[{"key": 1, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TOYOTA Connected Corporation", "date": "16 December 2022", "question": "1. Threat Model 2. Coding 3. Basic owasp top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 2, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "Atos", "date": "15 December 2022", "question": "C\u00f3mo te manejas cuando hay un problema donde hay que involucrar a m\u00e1s de uno en el equipo", "answer": []}, {"key": 3, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Ozow", "date": "15 December 2022", "question": "Technical interview covers cybersecurity (mainly AWS) concepts.", "answer": []}, {"key": 4, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Financeit", "date": "14 December 2022", "question": "Cant disclose NDA, sorry !", "answer": []}, {"key": 5, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "EcoVadis", "date": "12 December 2022", "question": "Will you be able to train other employees (share your knowledge)? Are you willing to take care of several security testing solutions that we currently have? In what areas would you like to expand your expertise?", "answer": []}, {"key": 6, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zalando", "date": "11 December 2022", "question": "Beyond what I could have imagined. Many technical questions (coming from my to-be line manager) had nothing to do with my role and responsibilities.", "answer": ["The best I could"]}, {"key": 7, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Boeing", "date": "8 December 2022", "question": "Tell me about your background?", "answer": []}, {"key": 8, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "8 December 2022", "question": "Azure AD scenario based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 9, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Mews", "date": "8 December 2022", "question": "There was a scenario based question, which asked my thought process and resolution, based on a security incident. Overall it tested my overall understanding around security processes already known.", "answer": ["My answers were closely tied to NIST security standards and frameworks."]}, {"key": 10, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NCS", "date": "8 December 2022", "question": "Q: Where do you see yourself in 5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 11, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Millicom", "date": "7 December 2022", "question": "experiencia en el campo y certificaciones acreditadas que poseo en el campo", "answer": []}, {"key": 12, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Canonical", "date": "6 December 2022", "question": "Asked to submit written Interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 13, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "League", "date": "5 December 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work for us", "answer": []}, {"key": 14, "position": "Security Correlation Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "2 December 2022", "question": "Azure sentinel and KQL questions", "answer": ["Based on experience"]}, {"key": 15, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "SIX", "date": "2 December 2022", "question": "What is your experience with Linux.", "answer": []}, {"key": 16, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Avnet", "date": "2 December 2022", "question": "\"How would you determine how many jelly beans will fit in a suitcase?\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 17, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "30 November 2022", "question": "Q: What could I bring to the table to help this technical team. Q: Questions about my previous experiences and how I went about resolving issues &amp; finding out technical info. I also asked several questions back to Citizens on company culture, working environment, and the opportunties I had to grow with the company.", "answer": []}, {"key": 18, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Jaguar Land Rover", "date": "30 November 2022", "question": "Are you OK to be relocated to the UK?", "answer": []}, {"key": 19, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Workhuman", "date": "30 November 2022", "question": "steps for achieving ISO27001 compliance", "answer": []}, {"key": 20, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Workhuman", "date": "30 November 2022", "question": "what is vulnerability? How would rate a vulnerability?", "answer": []}, {"key": 21, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Workhuman", "date": "30 November 2022", "question": "difference between risk and threat?", "answer": []}, {"key": 22, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flexport", "date": "28 November 2022", "question": "I signed an NDA. But nothing crazy.", "answer": []}, {"key": 23, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "NetBrain Technologies", "date": "28 November 2022", "question": "Research Paper explanation on Resume, HTTP vs HTTPS, TCP/IP Overview, Cryptography (Asym and Sym)", "answer": []}, {"key": 24, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Expleo Group", "date": "26 November 2022", "question": "Is snort the same as wireshark?", "answer": []}, {"key": 25, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "25 November 2022", "question": "Technical as well as personality questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 26, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DeepL", "date": "24 November 2022", "question": "The questions have covered everything from general views on the state of the art, to technical concepts, to detailed technical issues. The questions arose for the most part from an open conversation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 27, "position": "Cyber Security Support Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro Inc.", "date": "24 November 2022", "question": "-The technical assessment contains easy questions about networking, security, virtualization, database and coding -The second interview we had a chat about my experience , security in general, how firewalls work and how IPS/IDS work -The third interview was a managerial interview about the team and why I want to leave my current job, etc. In the end of it I was asked to create a presentation about their anti virus product Apex One -The fourth interview was the most hard one and the most technical, there were questions about basic Routing Security: General concepts like what is a vulnerability CIA GRC Fortinet firewalls: Difference between proxy mode and flow mode Linux: he got very specific on how to search in vim + the basic commands", "answer": []}, {"key": 28, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sandia National Laboratories", "date": "23 November 2022", "question": "What kinds of research projects would you propose as soon as you joined the team.", "answer": []}, {"key": 29, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "MongoDB", "date": "23 November 2022", "question": "I was asked about my interest on this role and my motivation to be part of the team/role, was asked about the information security concepts, OS related questions and few scenario based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 30, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Yext", "date": "22 November 2022", "question": "General cloud security architecture design questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 31, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "SIX", "date": "22 November 2022", "question": "Q: Talk about yourself and your studies Q: What did you do in your previous company? Q: (explains values of company) Could you see yourself working in this company, knowing its values? Q: If you have to pick up one of our 5 values, which one would it be and why? Q: What would you need to successfully work in a project? Q: What do you expect from the team? Q: What do you expect from the task/projects?", "answer": []}, {"key": 32, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Diconium", "date": "21 November 2022", "question": "Wie kann man eine Application vor Angriffen verteidigen?", "answer": []}, {"key": 33, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "ITC Infotech", "date": "20 November 2022", "question": "Basic Networking questions having knowledge in CCNA will aid to crack you interview if you know software like GS3 and cisco packet tracer is a plus and have knowledge on port security will also help a lot.", "answer": []}, {"key": 34, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "18 November 2022", "question": "What's the difference between TCP 3 handshake and4handshake", "answer": []}, {"key": 35, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lockheed Martin", "date": "17 November 2022", "question": "What previous technical projects have you worked on?", "answer": []}, {"key": 36, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "SeatGeek", "date": "16 November 2022", "question": "Review source code of application, explain vulnerabilities found.", "answer": []}, {"key": 37, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Uber", "date": "16 November 2022", "question": "Q: Have you done bug bounty before", "answer": []}, {"key": 38, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Activision Blizzard", "date": "15 November 2022", "question": "What is considered a low hanging fruit in security?", "answer": ["Anything that is a preventable vulnerability that can apply to anything from infrastructure based to user based. Less"]}, {"key": 39, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Safaricom", "date": "15 November 2022", "question": "They ask the typical questions about the role and what you are expected to do.", "answer": []}, {"key": 40, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ING", "date": "14 November 2022", "question": "there was technical questions mostly. and some soft skills questions as well.", "answer": []}, {"key": 41, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Peloton Interactive", "date": "13 November 2022", "question": "Tell us about your resume, and how it relates to the job description.", "answer": []}, {"key": 42, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Norfolk Southern", "date": "13 November 2022", "question": "Weird tests and lectures about management", "answer": []}, {"key": 43, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "13 November 2022", "question": "What is the difference between Authorization and Authentication?", "answer": []}, {"key": 44, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Rapid", "date": "10 November 2022", "question": "Why did you choose RapidAPI?", "answer": []}, {"key": 45, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "Looking at datavant\u2019s tenets, what would you away about being nice and getting things done or whatever", "answer": []}, {"key": 46, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "Looking at datavant\u2019s tenets, how wound you go about less rules and getting more done or whatever", "answer": []}, {"key": 47, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "What would your past supervisors say about you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 48, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "Tell me \u2026. What is your superpower?", "answer": []}, {"key": 49, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "Had networking, Linux, and windows server questions. Most are basic.", "answer": []}, {"key": 50, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "Mostly ethical hacking and pentesting questions in the web development field. Also questions regarding the software development process and security architecture.", "answer": []}, {"key": 51, "position": "ICS Security Engineer", "company": "Airbus", "date": "9 November 2022", "question": "What was the topic of interest for this job? What technical experience do you have?", "answer": []}, {"key": 52, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "HCL", "date": "8 November 2022", "question": "SDL and cyber security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 53, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HighRadius", "date": "7 November 2022", "question": "Fundamentals of security, Frame works, Next Gen tools", "answer": ["Good"]}, {"key": 54, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Qualys", "date": "6 November 2022", "question": "Asked general questions about experience.", "answer": ["I am a disabled veteran and HR never followed up with the hiring manager for an interview. Less"]}, {"key": 55, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Schneider Electric", "date": "5 November 2022", "question": "What was your most difficult customer experience and how did you resolve?", "answer": []}, {"key": 56, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "4 November 2022", "question": "What is your expected salary?", "answer": ["The salary is negotiable within market average. If you exaggerate your initial offer, you will automatically be rejected without any chance of a counter-offer or any further negotiation Less"]}, {"key": 57, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adarma", "date": "3 November 2022", "question": "Various technical &amp; security questions ranging from networking, operating systems, analytic response.", "answer": []}, {"key": 58, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "TikTok", "date": "1 November 2022", "question": "- Implement LRU - [1,1,2,3,3,3,4,4] -&gt; is ordered with in place swaps, reorder to have unique int at the start of the array - k8s ports etc. - General design like Kafka, endpoints etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 59, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Puget Sound Energy", "date": "31 October 2022", "question": "Personality question to see how you deal with people.", "answer": []}, {"key": 60, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ExtraHop Networks", "date": "31 October 2022", "question": "Perform mathematical operations in Python as indicated.", "answer": []}, {"key": 61, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "Expedia Group", "date": "30 October 2022", "question": "Architecture of Splunk. What is zero day attack? What is SSO &amp; SAML? What is a firewall. Difference in stateful and stateless firewall? What is Sql Injection ? Explain Log4j vulnerability? Incident Response Life Cycle? How to do host hardening? What is spoofing? Why are you looking for a change?", "answer": []}, {"key": 62, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Arcfield", "date": "29 October 2022", "question": "We just discussed my experience, how it would fit the role, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 63, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "28 October 2022", "question": "python/powershell coding", "answer": []}, {"key": 64, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "28 October 2022", "question": "analyse file", "answer": []}, {"key": 65, "position": "Sr Security Data Software Engineer", "company": "Databricks", "date": "28 October 2022", "question": "Coding questions were not algorithmic puzzles, but real life usage of calling web apis and processing data.", "answer": []}, {"key": 66, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Circle Internet Financial", "date": "27 October 2022", "question": "Essential security knowledge review and questions like \"Why Circle?\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 67, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "26 October 2022", "question": "How do you respond to incidents?", "answer": []}, {"key": 68, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "26 October 2022", "question": "they asked me 3 questions the first one was easy but the solutions requierd 3 nested loops. the secend i dont remember and the third one was finding the angle beetwen the hands of the clock", "answer": []}, {"key": 69, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DataDome", "date": "26 October 2022", "question": "- Why DataDome? - What makes you a good candidate for this role? - Technical questions about the role - Background and usual presentation questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 70, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 October 2022", "question": "IR, Protocols, Incident handling, Zero day, phishing", "answer": []}, {"key": 71, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "DTE Energy", "date": "25 October 2022", "question": "Give us an example of an obstacle you ran into and how was it overcome?", "answer": []}, {"key": 72, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Farm Credit Bank of Texas", "date": "24 October 2022", "question": "what is your experience with cloud security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 73, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Weights & Biases", "date": "24 October 2022", "question": "What sort of security signals would you monitor and track at a company?", "answer": []}, {"key": 74, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Lumen", "date": "23 October 2022", "question": "What have you done at different situations during previous jobs", "answer": []}, {"key": 75, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "23 October 2022", "question": "Do you have any experience with privacy engineering?", "answer": ["No"]}, {"key": 76, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "Riot Games", "date": "22 October 2022", "question": "Tell me about time when your experience at one company was beneficial at another company (something like that).", "answer": ["I talked about two SOC roles I consulted for at two different companies."]}, {"key": 77, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "22 October 2022", "question": "How would you secure a Data Centre?", "answer": []}, {"key": 78, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "BigID", "date": "21 October 2022", "question": "Asked questions mostly related to software composition analysis.", "answer": []}, {"key": 79, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "20 October 2022", "question": "how would you handle IR response?", "answer": []}, {"key": 80, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Aristocrat Technologies", "date": "20 October 2022", "question": "How would you run an incident/what do you look for.", "answer": []}, {"key": 81, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dante International", "date": "19 October 2022", "question": "What security measure can be put in place by an organization in order to prevent email spoofing?", "answer": []}, {"key": 82, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "SecureData", "date": "18 October 2022", "question": "What are some of the things you demostrate product knowledge to clients?", "answer": []}, {"key": 83, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "LeanIX", "date": "17 October 2022", "question": "From past experience, interviewer was struggling to figure out if I fit 100 percent with the technical requriments whereas I had done far more that what was required for this role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 84, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Wipro", "date": "13 October 2022", "question": "Firewalls, Network Security &amp; Network Architecture", "answer": []}, {"key": 85, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "SeatGeek", "date": "13 October 2022", "question": "1. First round was a Vulnerable Web Application Challenge. The time allotted for the round was 1 week and was a take-home test. Along with exploiting the application, a report had to be created for the challenge. 2. For the next round the interview got scheduled but the recruiter informed me that the position has already been filled.", "answer": ["Created a 10-page report which got me through to the next round."]}, {"key": 86, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "12 October 2022", "question": "TCP/IP questions. Threat modeling. Typical security Engineering questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 87, "position": "Senior Third Party Security Engineer Req ID: R0055963", "company": "eBay", "date": "11 October 2022", "question": "This is the first round of interview. I will be notified of next steps.", "answer": []}, {"key": 88, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "The Washington Post", "date": "11 October 2022", "question": "General stuff you should know. OWASP SANS25 Dug a bit deeper on encryption and certificates than you'd typically use day-to-day. Code review. Behavioral was by far the oddest, lots of tell me a specific case where you failed or X bad thing happened and how you handled that. IDK about you but in my work we typically get ahead of issues to prevent them from happening.", "answer": []}, {"key": 89, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "11 October 2022", "question": "Explain some Native Cloud Security Services?", "answer": []}, {"key": 90, "position": "Security DevOps Engineer", "company": "eToro Social Trading", "date": "10 October 2022", "question": "Home project Create a parsing and filtering mechanism to SIEM of Emails via GCP", "answer": ["Created GCP project and pulled all emails from my gmail inbox with Python. Filtered them by certain criteria / ML (optionally) Set up VM for SaS SIEM and via Python module and integrated with it and parsed the filtered mails I declared as SPAM. Less"]}, {"key": 91, "position": "Security Engineer Associate", "company": "Belvo", "date": "10 October 2022", "question": "- Why should Belvo hire me?\r\n- Why I am choosing Belvo\r\n- Which kind of business does Belvo impacts\r\n- Questions about Belvo main product", "answer": []}, {"key": 92, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "TuSimple", "date": "9 October 2022", "question": "Difference between TCP and UDP", "answer": []}, {"key": 93, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 October 2022", "question": "Standard security related questions. nothing unusual", "answer": []}, {"key": 94, "position": "Security Engineer - Penetration Testing", "company": "Amazon", "date": "7 October 2022", "question": "Web authentication,SSRF,CSRF,Scripting,Java code review,XSS,TLS handshake,encryption.Needed to have a very deep understanding of those.", "answer": []}, {"key": 95, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MongoDB", "date": "6 October 2022", "question": "Please describe some projects / initiatives you lead and any challenges that arose during the process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 96, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Edward Jones", "date": "5 October 2022", "question": "Situational questions. Not much technical", "answer": []}, {"key": 97, "position": "Sr. Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Red Ventures", "date": "5 October 2022", "question": "Explain your cloud cyber experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 98, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "5 October 2022", "question": "Q: How do ARP poisoning and DNS poisoning attacks work? Q: Tell me about a hard situation you had in your previous job.", "answer": []}, {"key": 99, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "10x Genomics", "date": "3 October 2022", "question": "The hiring manager will ask you all about the thread and process because it's his expertise :D I'm not sure how much would a Sec Engineer benefit from knowing thread/process while operating the Sec practices. I know it's a piece of it but not all, God! Ask, security questions please, you're not hiring a sys admin. I've had feedback from another friend that their approach to certain positions is not contemporary and they seem to be quite traditional. I will stay away from this company. I felt stressful during the interview.", "answer": []}, {"key": 100, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Astranis", "date": "3 October 2022", "question": "Went over my resume and talked about how great (!) the company is.", "answer": []}, {"key": 101, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Blue Shield Of California", "date": "3 October 2022", "question": "About my current role, how to secure systems, threat modeling.", "answer": []}, {"key": 102, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Binary Global", "date": "3 October 2022", "question": "Network basics firewalls packet flow", "answer": []}, {"key": 103, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Robert Bosch India", "date": "2 October 2022", "question": "project based questions and where do u see yourself in next 5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 104, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Cure.Fit", "date": "1 October 2022", "question": "1st Technical round will be more towards your basic vulnerabilities related to Access control, oauth, SAML etc and there mitigations. (Need to show them things practically). \r\n2nd round will be more about your approach and methodology, tools and techniques. APIs and Mobile Security, (again get ready for practical). Asked about the patches of the vulnerabilities without the help of firewall (WAF). \r\n3rd round will be more towards your cloud security skills.  You must have knowledge about the cloud services, and micro services and about their vulnerabilities. \r\nFew mixed questions from Active Directory, DevSecOps, Automation, and Language based questions. Few questions were from the post data breach and how to deal with the post data breach etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 105, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Bayer", "date": "1 October 2022", "question": "It varies based upon interviewer.", "answer": []}, {"key": 106, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lockheed Martin", "date": "29 September 2022", "question": "Behavioral questions and a couple technical questions about my coding language skills.", "answer": []}, {"key": 107, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Boeing", "date": "27 September 2022", "question": "What cyber security softwares/platforms have you used? What cyber related courses/certs do you plan to obtain before graduating?", "answer": []}, {"key": 108, "position": "Corporate Security Engineer", "company": "Highspot ", "date": "27 September 2022", "question": "Experience with 2 factor authentication?", "answer": []}, {"key": 109, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "7-Eleven", "date": "27 September 2022", "question": "Explain TLS Handshake in detail", "answer": []}, {"key": 110, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Keysight Technologies", "date": "26 September 2022", "question": "- General OWASP 10 \n- Little coding question", "answer": []}, {"key": 111, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "24 September 2022", "question": "scripting challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 112, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Databricks", "date": "23 September 2022", "question": "Security Domains, Culture Fit, Agile", "answer": []}, {"key": 113, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Bayzat", "date": "23 September 2022", "question": "What are JWTs used for? Authorization or Authentication?", "answer": []}, {"key": 114, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "HCLTech", "date": "23 September 2022", "question": "SQL injection, xss, card, owasp", "answer": ["I have answered all the questions"]}, {"key": 115, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Equinix", "date": "23 September 2022", "question": "A number of questions from unrelated subject areas.", "answer": []}, {"key": 116, "position": "Senior Network Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MetLife", "date": "21 September 2022", "question": "Basic technical questions in Networking and daily troubleshooting scenarios.", "answer": []}, {"key": 117, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "20 September 2022", "question": "Describe your experience with Python.", "answer": []}, {"key": 118, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Glassdoor", "date": "20 September 2022", "question": "I was asked about my experience with AWS, Security experience, familiarity with security tools.  Everything I would expect to be asked based on the job posting.", "answer": []}, {"key": 119, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "20 September 2022", "question": "- questions were asked on Network Security, Routers, Same origin policy, CORS, CSRF, XSS, How to secure Web Applications, Asymmetric vs symmetric encryption, OS security \n\nCoding question - port scanning", "answer": []}, {"key": 120, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adarma", "date": "20 September 2022", "question": "What are the different cloud offerings", "answer": []}, {"key": 121, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "19 September 2022", "question": "Defense -in-depth\r\nMitre Attack\r\nPort numbers(21,80,443 etc)", "answer": []}, {"key": 122, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Robert Bosch India", "date": "19 September 2022", "question": "DBMS, Networking, Cryptography, Network Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 123, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Wipro", "date": "18 September 2022", "question": "Most of them are Scenario based and some very basic questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 124, "position": "Consulting System Engineer - Security", "company": "Fortinet", "date": "16 September 2022", "question": "Perguntas de todos os tipos, sobre conhecimentos t\u00e9cnicos, entre outros.\r\nPerguntas foram feitas em portugu\u00eas, ingl\u00eas e tamb\u00e9m em espanhol.", "answer": []}, {"key": 125, "position": "Associate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "16 September 2022", "question": "Describe UDP.\nDescribe OSI model.", "answer": []}, {"key": 126, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "CertiK", "date": "15 September 2022", "question": "The motivation of research projects? \nSmart contract related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 127, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Lokalise", "date": "14 September 2022", "question": "Mostly just questions about my previous experience, and about the take-home task.", "answer": []}, {"key": 128, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ubuntu", "date": "9 September 2022", "question": "What is an exceptional thing you have done , starting from highscool?", "answer": []}, {"key": 129, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Mindtree", "date": "9 September 2022", "question": "Interviewer asked me about cyber attacks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 130, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "8 September 2022", "question": "I was asked to create a presentation on a topic and present it.", "answer": ["I created a presentation and stood up a PoC Demo of my work using FOSS and cloud hosting to demonstrate skill sets. Less"]}, {"key": 131, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Trade Republic", "date": "8 September 2022", "question": "Security Engineering topics, focused on cloud, infrastructure, application and general IT security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 132, "position": "Staff Information Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "7 September 2022", "question": "What is CMDB in ServiceNow", "answer": []}, {"key": 133, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Southern Company", "date": "7 September 2022", "question": "Networking related questions. IP address and subnet.", "answer": []}, {"key": 134, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Spotify", "date": "6 September 2022", "question": "What is the difference between a threat and a vulnerability?", "answer": ["A vulnerability is a weakness in a system that exposes a company to threats, and therefore increases the likelihood of a negative event. A threat is a negative event, such as the exploit of a vulnerability. Less"]}, {"key": 135, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Deimos ", "date": "6 September 2022", "question": "What drives you at work?", "answer": ["The desire to produce results and make myself better."]}, {"key": 136, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Deimos ", "date": "6 September 2022", "question": "Do you prefer working as a team or as an individual?", "answer": ["Both. Depending on the scenario. But team work yields better results due to collaboration Less"]}, {"key": 137, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Netskope", "date": "2 September 2022", "question": "knowledges in DB, Linux, Networking, Troubleshooting, Docker and Kubernetis", "answer": ["as far my knowledge was deeper in some topics i did face these questions with as much technical details as possible in order to show my skills on these topics Less"]}, {"key": 138, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "2 September 2022", "question": "All about security.\nCryptography.\nAttacks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 139, "position": "Information Security Engineer 3", "company": "WEX", "date": "1 September 2022", "question": "No interview was conducted until now.", "answer": []}, {"key": 140, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Paychex", "date": "31 August 2022", "question": "Questions were regarding the network side and Ports", "answer": ["I know all these and I have experience in network and security side in my previous job Less"]}, {"key": 141, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "American Association of Motor Vehicle Administrators", "date": "31 August 2022", "question": "Tell me about a project that you are proud of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 142, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "30 August 2022", "question": "What would you do if you were caught between requirements from engineering teams and compliance?", "answer": []}, {"key": 143, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "29 August 2022", "question": "TCP Handshake\nAsymmetric vs Symmetric Encryption\nLinux basic\nIncident Handling process", "answer": []}, {"key": 144, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "28 August 2022", "question": "Coding interview: build cli command CD", "answer": []}, {"key": 145, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "CoinDCX", "date": "26 August 2022", "question": "Practical knowledge based questions which requires practical and technical knowledge both.", "answer": []}, {"key": 146, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "26 August 2022", "question": "Tell me about a time when your view on something important was significantly changed by someone that came from a different perspective? What was your reaction? What made you change your mind?", "answer": []}, {"key": 147, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Yubi", "date": "26 August 2022", "question": "wanted to apply but backed off as it's not a remote first company.", "answer": []}, {"key": 148, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "State Farm", "date": "25 August 2022", "question": "Is ping a layer 3 or layer 4 protocol?", "answer": ["It's a layer 3, just for anyone who needs that information."]}, {"key": 149, "position": "Security Engineer II", "company": "Outreach", "date": "25 August 2022", "question": "bunch of questions about tools I've used... random questions about hashing. Some stuff about cross site scripting and how to prevent it. How you would run a VM process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 150, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Leidos", "date": "24 August 2022", "question": "Your Previous job experience that will benefit the job role.", "answer": ["I provided the similar task what I do from my past jobs (worth mentioning my security skills back ground). Less"]}, {"key": 151, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Workhuman", "date": "24 August 2022", "question": "Why did you choose Workhuman?", "answer": []}, {"key": 152, "position": "Security Engineer Penetration Tester - Junior", "company": "Seven Bridges", "date": "24 August 2022", "question": "What type of Sql injections do you know?", "answer": []}, {"key": 153, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "CoinDCX", "date": "24 August 2022", "question": "Sdlc process \r\nSecurity architecture \r\nCompletely all the modules of cybersecurity", "answer": []}, {"key": 154, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Itochu Techno-Solutions", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "What kind of projects I have worked on in my previous jobs and how did I accomplish some of the more difficult tasks given.", "answer": []}, {"key": 155, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "AgentSync", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "Have you had to troubleshoot SSO and was it for external clients or internal issues?", "answer": ["Yes, I had to assist clients with SSO issues for a particular SaaS application. Ive had to more recently assist with these issues internally as well. Less"]}, {"key": 156, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Next Ventures", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "Past experience related with the area of expertise.", "answer": []}, {"key": 157, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Next Ventures", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "Technical questions related with the offer defined by the client.", "answer": []}, {"key": 158, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Infor", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "Vulnerabilities management platform and approaches", "answer": []}, {"key": 159, "position": "Sr. Network Security Engineer", "company": "St. Jude Children's Research Hospital", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "Everything/question is situational based from how you would handle explaining high level implementations to an executive member of the organization to describe a time you went above and beyond.  Team interview:  10-15 situation questions.  Technical interview 6 questions to describe what is happening given a certain question and how would you handle it/your response.", "answer": ["I answered it based on personal work experiences related to the position"]}, {"key": 160, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Rapyd", "date": "23 August 2022", "question": "none none none noe none none", "answer": []}, {"key": 161, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "21 August 2022", "question": "While I don't want to give specifics, I enjoyed more of the open-ended questions, especially the technical ones. It allowed me to demonstrate my process of working through a problems.", "answer": []}, {"key": 162, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "EPAM Systems", "date": "20 August 2022", "question": "What I think about ML-based security solutions?", "answer": []}, {"key": 163, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "EPAM Systems", "date": "20 August 2022", "question": "How would I harden a Windows/Linux machine.", "answer": []}, {"key": 164, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "EPAM Systems", "date": "20 August 2022", "question": "How directory traversal works and how would i detect it in a SIEM (what logs would I see and what info in those logs)?", "answer": []}, {"key": 165, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "EPAM Systems", "date": "20 August 2022", "question": "Mention a few MITRE Attack Techniques from the Tactic they gave me.", "answer": []}, {"key": 166, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Pax8", "date": "20 August 2022", "question": "Q: Tell me what you know about Pax8", "answer": []}, {"key": 167, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "KloudOne", "date": "19 August 2022", "question": "How to improve Cloud security ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 168, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Vinted", "date": "19 August 2022", "question": "Tell us something about yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 169, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Ava Labs", "date": "18 August 2022", "question": "I can not remember any specific questions, but I will say it was mostly centered around the technology and projects I have implemented in the past and also what experience I had with the technologies they currently use.", "answer": []}, {"key": 170, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Munich Re", "date": "17 August 2022", "question": "They asked about my cyber security experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 171, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PetSmart", "date": "17 August 2022", "question": "What's the difference between SAML and OAuth/OIDC?", "answer": []}, {"key": 172, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer - Networks", "company": "Amazon", "date": "16 August 2022", "question": "A lot of scenario-based questions covering DNS, DHCP, NAT/PAT, BGP, bandwidth usage, IPSEC, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 173, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Informatica", "date": "16 August 2022", "question": "1. What are the different techniques of pentest you do on login page ? \r\n\r\n2. how to do you bypass xss protection to exploit ?\r\n\r\n3. Owasp related ..attack techniques, tools used, and its mitigations etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 174, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Juni Technology", "date": "15 August 2022", "question": "- What tools would you include in a security pipeline?\r\n- Can you describe what vulnerabilities exists in OWASPs Top 10 security risks?\r\n- What are common remediation techniques for the vulnerabilities you mentioned?\r\n- How do you secure an EC2 instance in AWS?\r\n- What role do you think IaC plays in setting up a secure cloud environment?", "answer": []}, {"key": 175, "position": "Security Engineer (f/m/d)", "company": "DeepL", "date": "15 August 2022", "question": "How do you keep up to date with security related news?", "answer": []}, {"key": 176, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Augmedix", "date": "13 August 2022", "question": "What is  SQLI & how to fix it?", "answer": ["SQLI refers to Standard Query Language Injection.  In multiple ways, sqli can be prevented. Less"]}, {"key": 177, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CrowdStrike", "date": "13 August 2022", "question": "NDA - signed non disclosure agreement", "answer": []}, {"key": 178, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "11 August 2022", "question": "Threat modelling\r\nSecure code review\r\nAuthorization\r\nOWASP Top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 179, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "11 August 2022", "question": "Can Tell me about yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 180, "position": "Senior Security Engineer - Ethical Hacking", "company": "Deltek", "date": "10 August 2022", "question": "Define Zero Trust Framework and how to apply it in a real world scenario", "answer": []}, {"key": 181, "position": "Developmental Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Deltek", "date": "9 August 2022", "question": "What is your vulnerability analysis experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 182, "position": "Developmental Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Deltek", "date": "9 August 2022", "question": "What would you do in these scenarios to scan your data?", "answer": []}, {"key": 183, "position": "Intern security Engineer", "company": "Databricks", "date": "9 August 2022", "question": "Build a web crawler that collects all links from web pages in o(n) time", "answer": []}, {"key": 184, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sportsbet.com.au", "date": "8 August 2022", "question": "ELB default security options\r\nS3 cross-account access even the ones that aren't in BP\r\nPython list functions, OOP concepts", "answer": []}, {"key": 185, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Robert Bosch", "date": "7 August 2022", "question": "What does ec2 means? Describe in detail?\r\nWhat does IDM means why was it instated?", "answer": []}, {"key": 186, "position": "Network & Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "4 August 2022", "question": "OSPF, Firewall concept , how ssl and 3 handshake works", "answer": []}, {"key": 187, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Adobe", "date": "1 August 2022", "question": "7 Layer Network OSI model", "answer": []}, {"key": 188, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Hotstar", "date": "28 July 2022", "question": "1)Why did you use WAF and what are the use cases it resolved.\r\n\r\n2)Questions on Iam access and deny policies.", "answer": []}, {"key": 189, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Immersive Labs", "date": "28 July 2022", "question": "Describe how you would add value", "answer": []}, {"key": 190, "position": "Security & SIEM Engineer", "company": "SoundCloud", "date": "28 July 2022", "question": "How many years of experience do you have with Splunk?", "answer": []}, {"key": 191, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Jamf", "date": "27 July 2022", "question": "How do you setup a WAF?\r\nWhat kind of configuration for blocking do you setup on a WAF?\r\nWhat is your experience with FedRAMP?\r\nDescribe your process in setting up security controls and how this applies to the wider organization.", "answer": []}, {"key": 192, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Defense Contract Management Agency", "date": "27 July 2022", "question": "Least privilege, NIST standards, processes", "answer": []}, {"key": 193, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Criteo", "date": "26 July 2022", "question": "The interviews were very open, starting from a scenario and adapting it following my answers.\r\nThe coding interview was asking for a code to update the color of a pixel in an image, and of all the piwel touching it in cascade.", "answer": []}, {"key": 194, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Bank of America", "date": "25 July 2022", "question": "Talk about a problem that you solved, and how you approached it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 195, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Seven Bridges", "date": "25 July 2022", "question": "HR part: \nCan you tell me more about projects you worked on during your studies?\nTechnical part : \nCan you tell me what is MFA?\nCan you tell me more about your diploma thesis research?", "answer": []}, {"key": 196, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Ava Labs", "date": "24 July 2022", "question": "Technical questions were related to the role requirement.", "answer": []}, {"key": 197, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "22 July 2022", "question": "How do you automate the false positive elimination", "answer": []}, {"key": 198, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Yelp", "date": "22 July 2022", "question": "Coding interview questions revolves around day-to-day realistic business needs.\r\nSystem design interview question was about designing large scale security system.", "answer": []}, {"key": 199, "position": "Lead Security Engineer - Applications Security", "company": "Eye Care Leaders", "date": "22 July 2022", "question": "Simple formal discussion to know each other and company. Its not Q&A type interview", "answer": ["About my job role, experiences, technologies I worked."]}, {"key": 200, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Delivery Hero", "date": "22 July 2022", "question": "In case of security incident what was the first action", "answer": []}, {"key": 201, "position": "Security Engineer (MTS-1)", "company": "Nutanix", "date": "21 July 2022", "question": "Web security (OWASP top 10) related questions.\nPrevention of common attacks.\nPrivilege Escalation/Post exploitation.\nNetwork security.\n\nThey showed me a request and response and asked me to find what can go wrong.", "answer": []}, {"key": 202, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "21 July 2022", "question": "OSI model\nTCP/IP UDP Handshakes\nPort numbers\nConcepts of basic network devices: Switch, Router, Firewall.", "answer": []}, {"key": 203, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Whatfix", "date": "21 July 2022", "question": "Threat model a login form, SOP, CORS etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 204, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Lumen", "date": "20 July 2022", "question": "Tell me about your background.", "answer": []}, {"key": 205, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Citadel Securities", "date": "19 July 2022", "question": "How do you do threat modeling?", "answer": ["I have explained describing my thought process of threat modeling whereas I think they were expects g formal threat modeling. Less"]}, {"key": 206, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "SAP", "date": "19 July 2022", "question": "Tell me about your self", "answer": []}, {"key": 207, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "19 July 2022", "question": "Make a linked list and develop it", "answer": []}, {"key": 208, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "17 July 2022", "question": "How to exploit SSRF vuln?", "answer": []}, {"key": 209, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "17 July 2022", "question": "Security domain related questions\r\nCoding on prime numbers and Fibonacci series\r\nWhat is data structure ?\r\nWhat is RDBMS and No SQL?", "answer": []}, {"key": 210, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GOAT Group", "date": "15 July 2022", "question": "When you type google into your browser bar and hit enter, what happens?", "answer": []}, {"key": 211, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Harvest", "date": "15 July 2022", "question": "Questions about previous experiences that align with the job description", "answer": []}, {"key": 212, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Harvest", "date": "15 July 2022", "question": "What happens when you click submit when logging in?", "answer": []}, {"key": 213, "position": "Security Compliance Engineer", "company": "Kyndryl", "date": "15 July 2022", "question": "If I had hands on experience in the technologies that they are operating.", "answer": []}, {"key": 214, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "Deimos ", "date": "14 July 2022", "question": "What keeps you going in your career?", "answer": []}, {"key": 215, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Intercom Enterprises", "date": "14 July 2022", "question": "Tell me about your responsibility?", "answer": []}, {"key": 216, "position": "Info Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "13 July 2022", "question": "What are some protocols you'd add to company", "answer": ["More Authenticators"]}, {"key": 217, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NTT DATA", "date": "13 July 2022", "question": "Security related and over all IT related.", "answer": ["Good"]}, {"key": 218, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "FIS", "date": "12 July 2022", "question": "It\u2019s all about security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 219, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Open Systems", "date": "11 July 2022", "question": "Break down a network into XYZ number of subnets with ABC hosts", "answer": []}, {"key": 220, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Other", "date": "11 July 2022", "question": "How can you define a secure code?", "answer": []}, {"key": 221, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fastly", "date": "10 July 2022", "question": "Describe how a malicious bot would attack a website.", "answer": []}, {"key": 222, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deriv.com", "date": "9 July 2022", "question": "Please write a paragraph about two (2) of your direct reports in your most recent job, indicating their position titles, length of service, strengths, shortcomings, and overall work performance.", "answer": []}, {"key": 223, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Kuehne+Nagel", "date": "8 July 2022", "question": "Was given a Cybersecurity home assignment task", "answer": []}, {"key": 224, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "8 July 2022", "question": "Scenario based troubleshooting questions, linux commands and basic networking knowledge.", "answer": []}, {"key": 225, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Nuvemshop", "date": "8 July 2022", "question": "Contar uma experiencia na carreira, de sucesso ou n\u00e3o que me gostei (ou n\u00e3o) de ter passado.", "answer": ["De forma descontra\u00edda com uma experiencia que marcou e muito minha trajet\u00f3ria profissional, gra\u00e7as a Deus marcou pro bem! Less"]}, {"key": 226, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Foxhole Technology", "date": "8 July 2022", "question": "Do you live near the office?", "answer": ["No"]}, {"key": 227, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "7 July 2022", "question": "What is a MITM attack ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 228, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "7 July 2022", "question": "Tell me about a time...", "answer": []}, {"key": 229, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Modivcare", "date": "7 July 2022", "question": "Scenario based  questions \r\nHow you secure your network", "answer": []}, {"key": 230, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wise", "date": "7 July 2022", "question": "You are given more work every day than can be done in a workday. What do you do?", "answer": []}, {"key": 231, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wise", "date": "7 July 2022", "question": "How do you cope with not reaching your goals due to the team getting more work than can be possibly done?", "answer": []}, {"key": 232, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "6 July 2022", "question": "Different network topologies and practical implementation", "answer": []}, {"key": 233, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Seven Bridges", "date": "6 July 2022", "question": "I was asked a good chunk of mixed resume based, scenario based, and behavior based questions. \n\n1. Do you have any experience with Ansible or xyz tool?\n2. Tell me about your experience with vuln management.\n3. Tell me about how would you patch a critical vuln. General approach especially when having to work together across different teams such as Dev Ops or Software Engineers. How do you handle potential downtime and communicate effectively? How do you assess the risks involved when dealing with other severity levels of vulns such as high, medium, and low?\n4. Trick question regarding what general resource is useful for password management and compliance.", "answer": []}, {"key": 234, "position": "Junior Security Infrastructure Engineer", "company": "Swiss Re", "date": "6 July 2022", "question": "- Tell me things about your career that aren't in your CV.\r\n- Tell me why you want to join Swiss Re.\r\n- Tell me a situation where you did something wrong and how you handled it.\r\n- Tell me one of your virtues and one of your defects.", "answer": []}, {"key": 235, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Navy Exchange", "date": "6 July 2022", "question": "Experience with ACAS and HBSS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 236, "position": "Lead Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Realtor.com", "date": "3 July 2022", "question": "How would you secure a public facing API", "answer": []}, {"key": 237, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "2 July 2022", "question": "How is your Day to Day?", "answer": []}, {"key": 238, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Rogers Communications", "date": "2 July 2022", "question": "What is the security triad?", "answer": ["Confidentiality, Integrity, Availability"]}, {"key": 239, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Samsara", "date": "1 July 2022", "question": "Not able to disclose, I signed an NDA.", "answer": []}, {"key": 240, "position": "Security Engineer - Governance, Risk & Compliance", "company": "DataDome", "date": "1 July 2022", "question": "typical inteview questions (career, interest, etc) as well as some GRC cybersecurity generic common questions (type of risk treatment, CIA triad, definition of threat, vulnerbaility, risk etc.)", "answer": []}, {"key": 241, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Roblox", "date": "30 June 2022", "question": "Online Assessment\nTechnical Interviews\nBehavioral Rounds\nBar Raiser Round.", "answer": []}, {"key": 242, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Optiver", "date": "30 June 2022", "question": "System design related to trading", "answer": []}, {"key": 243, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Visa Inc.", "date": "29 June 2022", "question": "steps of IR life cycle", "answer": []}, {"key": 244, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "28 June 2022", "question": "Walk me through the javascript of the communication channel a stored XXS attack uses to relay info back to the attacker.", "answer": ["I dont have Javascipt on my resume and am not a pen tester"]}, {"key": 245, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Airbnb", "date": "28 June 2022", "question": "What does belonging mean to you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 246, "position": "Security Design Engineer", "company": "GHD", "date": "27 June 2022", "question": "basic industry  standards questions and protocols", "answer": ["answered with my experience and knowldge"]}, {"key": 247, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "New York Digital Investment Group", "date": "22 June 2022", "question": "Typical technical security questions around encryption, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 248, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 June 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work for us?", "answer": []}, {"key": 249, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "21 June 2022", "question": "Code review, thread modeling y vulnerability management,", "answer": []}, {"key": 250, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Asembia", "date": "21 June 2022", "question": "Describe na time you failed", "answer": []}, {"key": 251, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "20 June 2022", "question": "1. Understanding on the background of device logs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 252, "position": "Security Correlation Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "20 June 2022", "question": "A lot, cant remember at this point. But knowledge based and behavioral questions will arrive", "answer": []}, {"key": 253, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Aptean", "date": "18 June 2022", "question": "Usual AppSec interview questions, nothing hard", "answer": []}, {"key": 254, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "Ant Group", "date": "17 June 2022", "question": "1. Introduce PoW/PoS/PBFT consensus algorithm.\n2. Introduce crypto wallet.", "answer": []}, {"key": 255, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Remote", "date": "16 June 2022", "question": "What can you give to Remote? \r\nWhy should we hire you?\r\nHow would you solver a certain situation?\r\nHow would you introduce a new process into the organisation?", "answer": []}, {"key": 256, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "16 June 2022", "question": "Why do we need to invest in cyber security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 257, "position": "Senior Security Software Engineer", "company": "Wind River", "date": "15 June 2022", "question": "What was your most changeling task in your current job? And they will ask deep details regarding this.", "answer": []}, {"key": 258, "position": "Senior Security Software Engineer", "company": "Wind River", "date": "15 June 2022", "question": "How will you implement a HA instance between two regions by using kafka and kubernetes clusters.", "answer": []}, {"key": 259, "position": "Security Automation Developer", "company": "Pfizer", "date": "15 June 2022", "question": "What happens if there is a zero day, how will you help to identify if that vulnerability is being exploited?", "answer": []}, {"key": 260, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "14 June 2022", "question": "How do I deal with difficult people?", "answer": ["I state the facts and explain my position and response"]}, {"key": 261, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "14 June 2022", "question": "What is your favorite algorithm?", "answer": []}, {"key": 262, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "State Street", "date": "14 June 2022", "question": "Old school interview with traditional situation based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 263, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AO", "date": "14 June 2022", "question": "What challenges did you experience and how did you overcome them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 264, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PPRO", "date": "13 June 2022", "question": "How would you hack an API", "answer": []}, {"key": 265, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Garrison Technology", "date": "13 June 2022", "question": "Lambda Captured Object Lifetimes (EXP61-CPP)", "answer": []}, {"key": 266, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "12 June 2022", "question": "The usual EEoC garbage HR people hide behind these days.", "answer": []}, {"key": 267, "position": "Junior Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "B&M Retail", "date": "12 June 2022", "question": "Pros and cons of certain virtualisation softwares \r\nWhat previous experience of security tooling do you have", "answer": []}, {"key": 268, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "10 June 2022", "question": "What is your best tools you used ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 269, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Capgemini", "date": "10 June 2022", "question": "So many questions were asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 270, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "KocharTech", "date": "9 June 2022", "question": "They ask about all most common vulnerabilities with examples", "answer": ["I told him all OWASP TOP 10 vulnerabilities with live examples.\r\nThat's it."]}, {"key": 271, "position": "Principal Security Software Engineer", "company": "Aurora Innovation", "date": "7 June 2022", "question": "Sum binary digits with Go.", "answer": []}, {"key": 272, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Atlan", "date": "7 June 2022", "question": "It was a discussion around the solutions I presented in the assignment.\nDeep knowledge around application security, cloud security and infrastructure security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 273, "position": "Junior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Talon.One", "date": "7 June 2022", "question": "Mention your contribution to your previous workplace.", "answer": ["Detecting the loophole like gaps in Password policy and implementing other policies like incident response policy.\r\nSecurity awareness training for all employees and a controlled Phishing campaign to help understand the efficiency of the training, Less"]}, {"key": 274, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Boston Consulting Group", "date": "6 June 2022", "question": "Why should you consider BCG?", "answer": ["career aspiration, work life balance and remote working"]}, {"key": 275, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "4 June 2022", "question": "Was asked to write code that could parse specific pieces of information from a log file, and talk through my thought process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 276, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "2 June 2022", "question": "Most questions were typical behavioral questions. The technical peer round was comprised of different troubleshooting scenario questions related to the experience listed on my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 277, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Viasat", "date": "2 June 2022", "question": "Symmetric vs asymmetric keys, port numbers, tcp vs udp, Linux commands, 3 way handshake", "answer": []}, {"key": 278, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Gympass", "date": "2 June 2022", "question": "Experi\u00eancias passadas, perguntas sobre criptografia e seus melhores usos, situa\u00e7\u00f5es hipot\u00e9ticas e poss\u00edveis controles de seguran\u00e7a.", "answer": []}, {"key": 279, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "1 June 2022", "question": "Basic appsec process and SSH protocol details", "answer": []}, {"key": 280, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "30 May 2022", "question": "Classic system design question but 10% perf/scaling focus, 90% security focus", "answer": []}, {"key": 281, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "30 May 2022", "question": "Implement a simple encryption algorithm", "answer": []}, {"key": 282, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "30 May 2022", "question": "Tell me about a past project you were particularly proud of", "answer": []}, {"key": 283, "position": "Linux Security Researcher/Engineer", "company": "Runecast", "date": "30 May 2022", "question": "Concise technical questions, also on the soft skills side you will be having some questions, but no worries it is a really pleasant interview process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 284, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "MoEngage", "date": "27 May 2022", "question": "1)Introduce yourself\r\n2)more about internship and what did you learned from that\r\n3)about CCNT certification\r\n4) ISO standards,remaining other standards\r\n5)IP addressing ranges\r\n6)OSI model\r\n7)switch\r\n8)router\r\n9)Hobbies\r\n10)why should we hire you", "answer": []}, {"key": 285, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datavant", "date": "27 May 2022", "question": "Mostly behavioral questions, disappointed by the lack of technical questions in the on-site.", "answer": []}, {"key": 286, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "26 May 2022", "question": "What is Asymmetric Cryptography and where is it used", "answer": []}, {"key": 287, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "OTORIO", "date": "26 May 2022", "question": "Tell us a tool you would use to attack AD", "answer": []}, {"key": 288, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TEKsystems", "date": "24 May 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work with our firm?", "answer": []}, {"key": 289, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TEKsystems", "date": "24 May 2022", "question": "I know the money is low, but it will grow over time. Are you comfortable taking a low offer to get your foot in the door with the client?", "answer": []}, {"key": 290, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "HashiCorp", "date": "23 May 2022", "question": "How do dynamically secure and store credentials used by a CI/CD pipeline to deploy infrastructure?", "answer": []}, {"key": 291, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PayScale", "date": "23 May 2022", "question": "Do you have any pets? If so, what do you have?", "answer": []}, {"key": 292, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PayScale", "date": "23 May 2022", "question": "Define the difference between risk and vulnerabilities.", "answer": []}, {"key": 293, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Wipro", "date": "23 May 2022", "question": "Self and roles and responsibilities", "answer": ["Good"]}, {"key": 294, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sandalwood Engineering & Ergonomics", "date": "23 May 2022", "question": "What experience do you bring to the role?", "answer": ["Answered and spoke about my resume."]}, {"key": 295, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EPAM Systems", "date": "20 May 2022", "question": "Que es un golden ticket?\r\npreguntas respecto al security de windows", "answer": []}, {"key": 296, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "19 May 2022", "question": ".", "answer": []}, {"key": 297, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "19 May 2022", "question": "Typical Amazon questions you can read about online using their STAR methodology.", "answer": []}, {"key": 298, "position": "Embedded Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Valeo", "date": "18 May 2022", "question": "Explain Secure boot functionality\r\nIs secoc needed for lin?", "answer": []}, {"key": 299, "position": "SecOps & Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Cyberbit", "date": "17 May 2022", "question": "What added value do you think you will bring to Cyberbit?", "answer": []}, {"key": 300, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Visa Inc.", "date": "16 May 2022", "question": "What's the difference between symmetric and asymmetric cryptography", "answer": []}, {"key": 301, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synergistic Systems", "date": "16 May 2022", "question": "About my general experience and cloud experience", "answer": ["I answered them well but they are prob looking for a cheaper engineer as most companies do not want to pay your actual worth. Less"]}, {"key": 302, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Samsung Electronics", "date": "15 May 2022", "question": "What is PIE mitigation in Linux", "answer": []}, {"key": 303, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Persistent Systems", "date": "13 May 2022", "question": "What is XSS. What is SQLi Some scenario based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 304, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GE", "date": "11 May 2022", "question": "All the OWASP top 10 attacks.\r\nWhat is CSRF, diving into each attack, how to resolve that, manipulate those attacks, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 305, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "10 May 2022", "question": "- Response codes from a web application\r\n- CORS\r\n- Explain XSS\r\n- difference between symmetric and assymetric encryption\r\n- explain PFS\r\n- explain CSRF", "answer": []}, {"key": 306, "position": "Principle Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "10 May 2022", "question": "Many questions around best practices within AWS and other cloud environments. Experience and background questions pretty basic stuff honestly.", "answer": []}, {"key": 307, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Northrop Grumman", "date": "10 May 2022", "question": "Experience with technical fields off the job posting", "answer": []}, {"key": 308, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "10 May 2022", "question": "Mostly technical deep dive inside", "answer": []}, {"key": 309, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "N26", "date": "10 May 2022", "question": "Lots of irrelevant questions about my previous jobs. Why did you left your company in 5 years ago?", "answer": []}, {"key": 310, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "9 May 2022", "question": "Sorting elements using heap algorithm.", "answer": []}, {"key": 311, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hastings Direct", "date": "9 May 2022", "question": "Way too many to recall anything specific, it was a barrage of questions.", "answer": ["Funny thing everyone else in the team, had an easy interview, none had previous cyber experience, IT degree or external security certificates that the manager said they had. Less"]}, {"key": 312, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Proton", "date": "9 May 2022", "question": "Questions about previous experience, open discussion.", "answer": []}, {"key": 313, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Poshmark", "date": "8 May 2022", "question": "Scenario based consultation \r\nRisk assessment process", "answer": []}, {"key": 314, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Crypto.com", "date": "7 May 2022", "question": "How to secure cloud apps", "answer": []}, {"key": 315, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "What is your work & team structure? (Like why?)", "answer": []}, {"key": 316, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "How many divisions do you have there? (Again why?)", "answer": []}, {"key": 317, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "What are the metrics and their mean in the tools you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 318, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "Difference between Authorization versus authentication?", "answer": []}, {"key": 319, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "Explain me OWASP Top 10, and pick any 3 to give details", "answer": []}, {"key": 320, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "How do you calculate CVSS score?", "answer": []}, {"key": 321, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "Pick any 1 from OWASP 10 and explain", "answer": []}, {"key": 322, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "How do you do code reviews? Because that\u2019s not how we do it here", "answer": []}, {"key": 323, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "Sql injection? Xss? Why would use Parameterized queries when you\u2019re already implementing prepared statements?", "answer": []}, {"key": 324, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "What is Authentication vs authorization?", "answer": []}, {"key": 325, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "6 May 2022", "question": "Hashing vs encryption? Where do you get salt from for hashing?", "answer": ["Walmart"]}, {"key": 326, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Whole Foods Market", "date": "5 May 2022", "question": "video interview process without human interaction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 327, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "WorkForce Software", "date": "5 May 2022", "question": "How would you reform our development process?  Explain TLS?  What is the difference between TLS 1.2 and 1.3", "answer": []}, {"key": 328, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "WorkForce Software", "date": "5 May 2022", "question": "How would you reform our development process?  Explain TLS?  What is the difference between TLS 1.2 and 1.3", "answer": []}, {"key": 329, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "3 May 2022", "question": "The take-home test is unrealistic with just an hour for coding+log analysis+MCQs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 330, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "2 May 2022", "question": "Describe which vulnerabilities you have most enjoyed exploiting in the past.", "answer": []}, {"key": 331, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "2 May 2022", "question": "Describe which vulnerabilities you have most enjoyed exploiting in the past.", "answer": []}, {"key": 332, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "1 May 2022", "question": "Perform code reviews of the below sample code.", "answer": []}, {"key": 333, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "AppsFlyer", "date": "1 May 2022", "question": "Two sum\nFind all paths", "answer": []}, {"key": 334, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Visa Inc.", "date": "29 April 2022", "question": "Are you willing to relocate to CA?", "answer": []}, {"key": 335, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Parsley Health", "date": "29 April 2022", "question": "What made you apply to Parsley Health?", "answer": []}, {"key": 336, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ISAC", "date": "29 April 2022", "question": "If you had a book, how many words would apoear the mostw.", "answer": []}, {"key": 337, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "29 April 2022", "question": "What have you done in the past", "answer": []}, {"key": 338, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Shopmonkey", "date": "29 April 2022", "question": "AppSec implementation, Security best practices, Different type of vulnerabilities and possible mitigation steps, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 339, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "CertiK", "date": "28 April 2022", "question": "The first round is simply an LC Easy question; the second round is asking about multiple items on the resume while about the knowledge rigority in PL.", "answer": []}, {"key": 340, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Integrity360", "date": "27 April 2022", "question": "Different type of network attacks and web applications. \r\nTell me about a time when.. questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 341, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AutoScout24", "date": "27 April 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work for AutoScout24?\r\nWhere do you see yourself in the next 5 years?", "answer": ["Since I had major interest in Cybersecurity,  I want to pursue, learn and grow my career in Cybersecurity and this job provides me the platform and the opportunity to improve my skills. Less"]}, {"key": 342, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Citrix", "date": "26 April 2022", "question": "Asked about web application security concepts around Same origin policy, Cross origin sharing and Content security policy.", "answer": []}, {"key": 343, "position": "Security Engineer, Digital Bank", "company": "SeaMoney", "date": "25 April 2022", "question": "No interview questions were given.", "answer": []}, {"key": 344, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Guild Education", "date": "25 April 2022", "question": "1. What's your experience with ___ tools?\n2. Have you used ___ before?", "answer": []}, {"key": 345, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Guild Education", "date": "25 April 2022", "question": "1. What's your experience with ___ tools?\n2. Have you used ___ before?", "answer": []}, {"key": 346, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Celonis", "date": "25 April 2022", "question": "What experience do you have in AWS?", "answer": []}, {"key": 347, "position": "iOS Security Engineer", "company": "Binance", "date": "25 April 2022", "question": "Reverse engineering iOS binaries, communications, security vulnerabilities, webviews, cryptography, SSL/TLS implementation and pinning", "answer": []}, {"key": 348, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Concentrix", "date": "24 April 2022", "question": "On basics of TCP/ ip, troubleshooting scenarios, and case management on escalations", "answer": []}, {"key": 349, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Nubank", "date": "24 April 2022", "question": "Conhecimento em ingles\r\nCase de sucesso \r\nTrabalho sobre press\u00e3o \r\nPrioriza\u00e7\u00e3o de trabalho", "answer": []}, {"key": 350, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "23 April 2022", "question": "2 Indians asked silly security question", "answer": []}, {"key": 351, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Talon.One", "date": "23 April 2022", "question": "Questions related to:\r\n- Introduction and explanation of the experience that\u2019s relevant to the job description \r\n- Salary expectations \r\n- A few technical questions to test basic understanding of the industry", "answer": []}, {"key": 352, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Kraken Digital Asset Exchange", "date": "22 April 2022", "question": "There was a NdA. However you can expect questions related to the job offer.", "answer": []}, {"key": 353, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Honeywell", "date": "22 April 2022", "question": "What drew you to Honeywell?", "answer": ["I was initially impressed with their technology and innovation sectors and the variety of fields Honeywell touches. Less"]}, {"key": 354, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ntt Security", "date": "22 April 2022", "question": "You can ping outside but not able to access webpage. What would be the issue?", "answer": ["Looks like a DNS issue, ping DNS and then check if DNS resolves the IPs."]}, {"key": 355, "position": "Security Software Research Engineer", "company": "Stellar Cyber", "date": "21 April 2022", "question": "easy leetcode coding questions, research background, domain knowledge, experience.  But do not waste your time, they are not honoring your experience and lying to you. No future start-up, one word-- run!", "answer": []}, {"key": 356, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "CoinDCX", "date": "20 April 2022", "question": "Questions based on Cyber attacks and live Examples", "answer": []}, {"key": 357, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CoinDCX", "date": "20 April 2022", "question": "Q. How do you steal clipboard data on iOS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 358, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "20 April 2022", "question": "threat model a diagram they show you", "answer": []}, {"key": 359, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Talent500", "date": "20 April 2022", "question": "How to secure an application before deployment?", "answer": ["Asked questions to understand the architecture first.\r\nThen provided steps for Threat Modelling, Pen testing, software composition analysis and risk assessment methodologies. Less"]}, {"key": 360, "position": "IT Security Engineer II", "company": "Datadog", "date": "19 April 2022", "question": "What is a situation where you feel like your interpersonal skills have had a positive impact on your team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 361, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "BigID", "date": "19 April 2022", "question": "My strengths and weaknesses because BigID sees the culture as a priority, which was a positive point in my final decision.", "answer": []}, {"key": 362, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Best Egg", "date": "16 April 2022", "question": "Basic cloud security questions, not difficult at all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 363, "position": "Espionage Security Engineer Investigator", "company": "Meta", "date": "16 April 2022", "question": "Questions related to understanding of security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 364, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "10x Genomics", "date": "15 April 2022", "question": "The head of security kept asking about computer parts and processes. He never asked about attack types probably because he is not from the cyber field specifically. That raises the issue when the title makes you head of security but not an expert of security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 365, "position": "Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "14 April 2022", "question": "I had a hacker rank challenge. They they scheduled a 45 mins technical interview and a 45 mins behavioral interview.", "answer": []}, {"key": 366, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Millennium Trust Company", "date": "14 April 2022", "question": "How would you assess and secure an acquired company and integrate their existing applications into the current infrastructure", "answer": []}, {"key": 367, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Millennium Trust Company", "date": "14 April 2022", "question": "What is one soft skill you would need to improve in order move to your next role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 368, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Millennium Trust Company", "date": "14 April 2022", "question": "What is a project you are most proud of and what was its final result", "answer": []}, {"key": 369, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Millennium Trust Company", "date": "14 April 2022", "question": "How would you pivot an internal cloud application to public facing and secure it", "answer": []}, {"key": 370, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Amazon", "date": "13 April 2022", "question": "what steps will you take to eliminate vulnerabilities from a program.", "answer": []}, {"key": 371, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Netskope", "date": "13 April 2022", "question": "What is TCP IP handshake", "answer": []}, {"key": 372, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Poshmark", "date": "13 April 2022", "question": "Out of bound SSRF, SQLI, RCE, writeups", "answer": []}, {"key": 373, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Movate", "date": "12 April 2022", "question": "How\u2019s success related to your passion?", "answer": []}, {"key": 374, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "South 6", "date": "12 April 2022", "question": "What is it about this organization that interests you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 375, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Avature", "date": "12 April 2022", "question": "How would you troubleshoot a linux system boot failure related to a file creation problem (not related to fs permissions) without investigating in the internet?", "answer": []}, {"key": 376, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Splunk", "date": "11 April 2022", "question": "Due to NDA can not talk too much, but they simply are 1 easy and 2 medium lc questions in the tech round.", "answer": []}, {"key": 377, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tencent", "date": "9 April 2022", "question": "Describe your project, the vulnerabilities you found, and how did you choose the targets.", "answer": []}, {"key": 378, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Auth0", "date": "7 April 2022", "question": "How do you keep passwords secure?", "answer": ["Lots of investigation here of bcrypt and rainbow tables and the value of salting and peppering etc. Less"]}, {"key": 379, "position": "Network Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Vimeo", "date": "6 April 2022", "question": "Do you know about x security software", "answer": []}, {"key": 380, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "6 April 2022", "question": "What happens when you type www.google.com?", "answer": []}, {"key": 381, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "6 April 2022", "question": "the main thing they focused in on the Scenario based question. Like what kind of issue if have faced and what have you done to resolve that.", "answer": []}, {"key": 382, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Brightsight", "date": "5 April 2022", "question": "Why are you into cyber security?\r\nWhat can you bring to the company?\r\nWhat is your career plan?", "answer": []}, {"key": 383, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Kraken Digital Asset Exchange", "date": "5 April 2022", "question": "How would you simulate an attack on Kraken?", "answer": []}, {"key": 384, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "D3 Security Management Systems", "date": "4 April 2022", "question": "Your biggest project and how you delivered it on time", "answer": []}, {"key": 385, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Deloitte", "date": "3 April 2022", "question": "Explain a P! t-shoot scenario.", "answer": []}, {"key": 386, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Optiv", "date": "3 April 2022", "question": "Explain a scenario where had to trouble shoot a P1 security incident", "answer": []}, {"key": 387, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "How do you remediate XSS?", "answer": ["Input validation - prefer a allowlist approach. However there are situations where allowlist is not possible and for those cases, denylist can be used.\nAlso make sure to encode the output, based on the context. So if the user input is going into html, then do hfml encoding of the data and so on Less"]}, {"key": 388, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "How to remediate Session fixation", "answer": ["Make sure the application session ids are not guessable, new sessionids are generated after every login Less"]}, {"key": 389, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "What does HSTS Header do? How do u set it?", "answer": ["Strict transport security when set makes sure the browser doesnt send traffic to domain on http. Always sends the traffic on https. \n\nIt can be set using the strict-transport-security header in the response, which includes a max-age and other directives like includesSubDomains \nAnother way is to get your certs included into the browser\u2019s prelist. Less"]}, {"key": 390, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "What TLS version do you recommend", "answer": ["TLS 1.2 and above"]}, {"key": 391, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "Scenario: describe what issues you might try to identify on a simple login page. 2 text boxes, 2 buttons on the page.", "answer": ["Sqli, user enumeration, misconfigured endpoint (http), forceful browing to authenticated pages, a low risk self XSS, etc Less"]}, {"key": 392, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "SentinelOne ", "date": "2 April 2022", "question": "Questions about background and experience with various software and technology.", "answer": []}, {"key": 393, "position": "Distributed Systems Software Engineer - API Security", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "1 April 2022", "question": "Some basic questions, such as, tell me about your self, what is your most interested experience, describe your working day, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 394, "position": "Senior Security Software Engineer", "company": "Grafana Labs", "date": "1 April 2022", "question": "Didn't really get to that stage.", "answer": ["None"]}, {"key": 395, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "P\\S\\L Group", "date": "31 March 2022", "question": "What does AppSec mean to you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 396, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "P\\S\\L Group", "date": "31 March 2022", "question": "What is your opinion on serverless and security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 397, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cofense", "date": "31 March 2022", "question": "Question about S3 bucket permission", "answer": []}, {"key": 398, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "xChange Solutions", "date": "31 March 2022", "question": "Biggest strength and weakness\r\nCareer goals\r\nSalary\r\nMotivation", "answer": []}, {"key": 399, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Red Hat", "date": "31 March 2022", "question": "Do you have experience with Openshift?", "answer": []}, {"key": 400, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Orion Innovation", "date": "30 March 2022", "question": "Related to f5 ltm and gtm", "answer": []}, {"key": 401, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Genesys", "date": "30 March 2022", "question": "I will not tell the specific questions but one must go through Network Security, Web Development and security, Cryptography basics and their resume and a little about the role.", "answer": ["You will find various sites on Google."]}, {"key": 402, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CRITICALSTART", "date": "30 March 2022", "question": "what is a vulnerability and risk", "answer": ["a coding flow or misconfiguration that can be exploited"]}, {"key": 403, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hounslow and Richmond Community Healthcare", "date": "30 March 2022", "question": "What projects have i worked on and how did i carry out the work load?", "answer": []}, {"key": 404, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Version 1", "date": "29 March 2022", "question": "Basics of cyber security\r\nIT experience\r\nISO and NIST frameworks", "answer": []}, {"key": 405, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "29 March 2022", "question": "How to un-dafang a defanged IP address.", "answer": []}, {"key": 406, "position": "Graduate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "BAE Systems", "date": "29 March 2022", "question": "Describe a time in your life where you chose to do a more difficult task, when an easier option was available", "answer": []}, {"key": 407, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Shipt", "date": "28 March 2022", "question": "Where do I see myself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 408, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Electronic Arts", "date": "28 March 2022", "question": "So I signed an NDA, but ill give a gist of how to help. \r\n1. Make sure you learn all the responsibilities necessary for the role \r\n2. search up top cyber security and networking security interview questions and go through it, make sure you can answer 90%  of those questions \r\n3. learn about dockers and web containerization as a whole \r\n4. make sure you are outgoing and comfortable during the interview.\r\n5. Learn about SIEM and different attack frameworks", "answer": []}, {"key": 409, "position": "Advanced Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Honeywell", "date": "28 March 2022", "question": "Most of the questions were related to the work I am currently doing and only theroretical questions was regarding the seminars which I presented many years back in the college days.", "answer": []}, {"key": 410, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Plaid", "date": "26 March 2022", "question": "Can you tell me about a time on a project where you wished you had done something differently?", "answer": []}, {"key": 411, "position": "Security Software QA Engineer", "company": "ScienceLogic", "date": "25 March 2022", "question": "Tell me about your experience with your past internship", "answer": ["I was an intern for VCU engineering as a security intern. I worked on a project to scan to the google playstore and look for malicious applications that request for permission access that does not align with the app's intended purposes. Less"]}, {"key": 412, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "What is your general approach to assessing the security of an application?", "answer": []}, {"key": 413, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Citi", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "What port does icmp use.", "answer": ["I told them that icmp is a protocol, and doesn't use the same notion of ports like tcp/udp.   However, it is often shown as port 0 in certain vendors logs.   It's really a type 0,1,3,8 or some combination of those that they are looking for, not port. Less"]}, {"key": 414, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Linode", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "General Linux questions/relevant experience. security concepts", "answer": []}, {"key": 415, "position": "Enterprise Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "What is your knowledge on ZTNA and why is that better?", "answer": []}, {"key": 416, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Altair Engineering", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "How to manage a multi-cloud environment?", "answer": []}, {"key": 417, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "24 March 2022", "question": "Describe the benefits of threat modelling", "answer": []}, {"key": 418, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Optiv", "date": "23 March 2022", "question": "Asked to follow the path of a packet", "answer": []}, {"key": 419, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NCI Agency", "date": "23 March 2022", "question": "Vragen over aanpak technisch en soft skills werden ook bevraagd", "answer": []}, {"key": 420, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "JumpCloud", "date": "22 March 2022", "question": "Do you have any experience with reverse engineering?", "answer": []}, {"key": 421, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "22 March 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work for Box?", "answer": []}, {"key": 422, "position": "Fire and Security Service Engineer", "company": "Modis", "date": "22 March 2022", "question": "History, experiences,  and what I'm looking for", "answer": []}, {"key": 423, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "22 March 2022", "question": "STAR questions around their leadership principles.", "answer": []}, {"key": 424, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "21 March 2022", "question": "Questions on TCP/IP and other networking", "answer": []}, {"key": 425, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "20 March 2022", "question": "What would you do if someone disagreed with you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 426, "position": "Product Security Engineer PSIRT", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "19 March 2022", "question": "We went over hypothetical situations where a bug was reported to go along with a code review. I found this very fun and challenging.", "answer": []}, {"key": 427, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "19 March 2022", "question": "1. What do you think you will be in 5 years time?", "answer": []}, {"key": 428, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Schr\u00f6dinger", "date": "19 March 2022", "question": "Explain your work flow and project", "answer": []}, {"key": 429, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "17 March 2022", "question": "Had to sign a non disclosure agreement, thus I cannot disclose details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 430, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "17 March 2022", "question": "Explain concepts of threat modelling. \r\nExplain how HTTPs works", "answer": []}, {"key": 431, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Wazuh", "date": "16 March 2022", "question": "Diferencia entre hashing, encryption y Encoding", "answer": []}, {"key": 432, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Fifth Third", "date": "16 March 2022", "question": "What is your experience with [insert system here]?", "answer": []}, {"key": 433, "position": "Security Engineering - Senior Engineer", "company": "Telstra", "date": "15 March 2022", "question": "What is CIA as it applies to security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 434, "position": "Security Engineering - Senior Engineer", "company": "Telstra", "date": "15 March 2022", "question": "Troubleshoot an application that wasn't responding at all", "answer": []}, {"key": 435, "position": "Security Engineering - Senior Engineer", "company": "Telstra", "date": "15 March 2022", "question": "What is the difference between a vulnerability and an exploit?", "answer": []}, {"key": 436, "position": "Network Security Engineer L2", "company": "Javi Systems", "date": "15 March 2022", "question": "Networking concepts, Cisco R & S\r\nSecurity related, Firewall and security device configuration and troubleshoot.", "answer": ["As  per the question I was explained."]}, {"key": 437, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "What got you interested in security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 438, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "An easy leetcode coding problem", "answer": ["An array/string problem that required recursion/backtracking to solve"]}, {"key": 439, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "Find security flaws in code", "answer": ["Looked through code and pointed out what I thought were flaws, and mentioned how developers could improve them. Less"]}, {"key": 440, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "How would you hack a system?", "answer": ["Look for common vulnerabilities first. Social engineering."]}, {"key": 441, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Optimizely", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "Questions about control vs compliance, questions on scripting and automation, dug into knowledge of AWS/Cloud services and general TCP/IP knowledge.", "answer": []}, {"key": 442, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Rebellion Defense", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "Generic questions regarding experience, can't disclose particulars due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 443, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Rebellion Defense", "date": "14 March 2022", "question": "Generic questions regarding experience, can't disclose particulars due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 444, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "13 March 2022", "question": "- Coding: general parsing log files and looking for patterns, some basic ciphers, SQL queries\r\n- Security based questions: drilling into TLS, DNS covered channels, high level questions about building security program for a small size company", "answer": []}, {"key": 445, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sprig", "date": "12 March 2022", "question": "A light coding question around parsing a file, secure design, adding security checks to developer workflows, and one behavioral interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 446, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "12 March 2022", "question": "OAuth vs SAML and details thereof. Java code read for security flaws. AWS architecture.", "answer": ["Very directly gave technical details you would learn in any technical documentation. Less"]}, {"key": 447, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Freshworks", "date": "12 March 2022", "question": "Microservices communication, architecture, authentication protocol, etc", "answer": ["I am not well prepared"]}, {"key": 448, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "10x Banking", "date": "11 March 2022", "question": "I cannot disclose due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 449, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Pluralsight", "date": "10 March 2022", "question": "A threat modelling case study\r\nActual developer type interaction", "answer": []}, {"key": 450, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "10 March 2022", "question": "Tell me a little bit about your recent experience and what you've been doing.", "answer": []}, {"key": 451, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Railsbank", "date": "10 March 2022", "question": "What is PCIDSS\r\nHow will secure a new cloud account and what are some of the native cloud security tools.\r\nThreat modeling questions\r\nSDLC question", "answer": []}, {"key": 452, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Digital Hands", "date": "8 March 2022", "question": "A bunch of technical question and telling me that they have a lot of projects. Good luck finding a person that knows as much as I but know all the technologies and a pie in the sky!", "answer": ["I answered the questions well. Yes I dont have 5 years of Fortigate experience, it clearly stated this in my resume. Less"]}, {"key": 453, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "TuSimple", "date": "5 March 2022", "question": "Q: Tell me your background , what you did and what's your interested field of security", "answer": []}, {"key": 454, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Cognizant Technology Solutions", "date": "3 March 2022", "question": "How to find vulnerability threats in any kind of database  ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 455, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "3 March 2022", "question": "Behavioral questions that asks STAR type questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 456, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Security Innovation", "date": "2 March 2022", "question": "Is prime, where you need to tell if an integrer is prime", "answer": []}, {"key": 457, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Babylon", "date": "1 March 2022", "question": "Java Backend multiple choice questions and competitive programming, which are irrelevant for application security.", "answer": ["Since it is irrelevant test AppSec engineer, I skipped it."]}, {"key": 458, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CITIC Group", "date": "1 March 2022", "question": "Self introduction and some questions about firewall and network", "answer": []}, {"key": 459, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Beacon (United Kingdom)", "date": "28 February 2022", "question": "Questions related to real world security experience.", "answer": ["I provided my experiences dealing cyber threats and attacks."]}, {"key": 460, "position": "Security Infrastructure Engineer", "company": "Bloomreach", "date": "27 February 2022", "question": "How did you handle failure in the past and what was the lesson learned?", "answer": []}, {"key": 461, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Regions Financial", "date": "27 February 2022", "question": "Networking questions, Past working experience, good knowledge of your projects.", "answer": []}, {"key": 462, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Regions Financial", "date": "27 February 2022", "question": "Networking questions, Past working experience, good knowledge of your projects.", "answer": []}, {"key": 463, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 February 2022", "question": "The standard \"what can you bring to the role.....\"", "answer": ["The (my) standard \"Exaggeration on my ability to fulfil the requirements...\""]}, {"key": 464, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "26 February 2022", "question": "Pourquoi Apple et pourquoi changer d\u2019entreprise", "answer": []}, {"key": 465, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "26 February 2022", "question": "Quelles failles de s\u00e9curit\u00e9 as tu trouv\u00e9 auparavant ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 466, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "FICO", "date": "26 February 2022", "question": "basic cyber security questions on networking edr", "answer": []}, {"key": 467, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "FICO", "date": "26 February 2022", "question": "basic cyber security questions on networking edr", "answer": []}, {"key": 468, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "NBCUniversal", "date": "25 February 2022", "question": "Typical behavioral and situational\r\n\r\nQuestions about experience outlined on my resume\r\n\r\nHow common network exploits are carried out and their effects\r\n\r\nSecurity appliance configuration questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 469, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "25 February 2022", "question": "Objetivos\r\nD\u00f3nde te ves dentro de 10 a\u00f1os\r\nExperiencia t\u00e9cnica", "answer": []}, {"key": 470, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "24 February 2022", "question": "Why do you want to work at Netflix?", "answer": []}, {"key": 471, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Krisp", "date": "24 February 2022", "question": "Q: The difference of authentication and authorization.\r\nQ: Do I know JavaScript?", "answer": []}, {"key": 472, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Krisp", "date": "24 February 2022", "question": "What do you expect from Krisp.", "answer": []}, {"key": 473, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Krisp", "date": "24 February 2022", "question": "What web vulnerabilities  do you know, describe them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 474, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Linode", "date": "22 February 2022", "question": "Do you have any experience with Penetration testing?", "answer": []}, {"key": 475, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Linode", "date": "22 February 2022", "question": "Do you have any experience with automation?", "answer": []}, {"key": 476, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Linode", "date": "22 February 2022", "question": "Do you have any experience with linux? How many years? What type of work have you done on linux?", "answer": []}, {"key": 477, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "NCC Group", "date": "22 February 2022", "question": "Ransonware an\u00e1lisis.\r\nMacros vulnerabilidades y soluciones\r\nReporte t\u00e9cnico", "answer": []}, {"key": 478, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "ChartHop", "date": "21 February 2022", "question": "As a security engineer, how comfortable do you feel writing full-stack code to be shipped with the product?", "answer": []}, {"key": 479, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "Kudelski Security", "date": "18 February 2022", "question": "What made you want to apply for this job?", "answer": []}, {"key": 480, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "18 February 2022", "question": "they never ask right question, very bad in irrelevant", "answer": []}, {"key": 481, "position": "Senior Security Engineer, Detection and Response", "company": "Coalition", "date": "17 February 2022", "question": "Basic questions like background and skills", "answer": []}, {"key": 482, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Humana", "date": "17 February 2022", "question": "It was more of a conversation honestly, getting to know me and my experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 483, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "16 February 2022", "question": "What is a problem i solved affected my job?", "answer": []}, {"key": 484, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Quantumscape", "date": "16 February 2022", "question": "If you want to improve on one thing, what would it be?", "answer": []}, {"key": 485, "position": "Senior DevSecOps Engineer: Container Security", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "15 February 2022", "question": "What are the differences between AWS Security Groups and Network ACLs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 486, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "WSO2", "date": "14 February 2022", "question": "Security Operations center experience\r\nLateral movement\r\nVulnerability management\r\nScripting\r\nSenario Based cloud security incidents", "answer": []}, {"key": 487, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "13 February 2022", "question": "vk", "answer": []}, {"key": 488, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Hospitality Digital", "date": "11 February 2022", "question": "Tell about yourself?\r\nWhy are you looking for a new job?\r\nQuestions about cloud security", "answer": []}, {"key": 489, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Texas Womans University", "date": "11 February 2022", "question": "Describe the TLS handshake process?", "answer": ["Answered with detailed TLS handshake"]}, {"key": 490, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Texas Womans University", "date": "11 February 2022", "question": "Describe the TLS handshake process?", "answer": ["Answered with detailed TLS handshake"]}, {"key": 491, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Afterpay", "date": "11 February 2022", "question": "Basic profile review and description of the job", "answer": []}, {"key": 492, "position": "Sr. Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Visa Inc.", "date": "10 February 2022", "question": "Questions were centered around the candidate's awareness of certain technologies.", "answer": []}, {"key": 493, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "CrowdStrike", "date": "10 February 2022", "question": "under NDA, can't answer, sorry.", "answer": []}, {"key": 494, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "CrowdStrike", "date": "10 February 2022", "question": "under NDA, can't answer, sorry.", "answer": []}, {"key": 495, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Morgan Stanley", "date": "10 February 2022", "question": "Standard background questions with salary requirements.\r\n\r\nSalary range was lower than what was originally stated by the recruiter.", "answer": []}, {"key": 496, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "9 February 2022", "question": "What is the sudo? What is the DNS?", "answer": []}, {"key": 497, "position": "Cyber Security Incident Response Engineer", "company": "Cruise", "date": "9 February 2022", "question": "none. Covered under NDA so I cannot discuss.", "answer": []}, {"key": 498, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Sprinklr", "date": "8 February 2022", "question": "Tell me about a time that you did something creative.", "answer": []}, {"key": 499, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Nava", "date": "8 February 2022", "question": "No interview was performed at all", "answer": []}, {"key": 500, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "eMudhra", "date": "7 February 2022", "question": "the interviewer asked all the  job processes which I've done in the previous company", "answer": []}, {"key": 501, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "DTCC", "date": "7 February 2022", "question": "How do you troubleshoot a problem?", "answer": ["Live example based on your experience"]}, {"key": 502, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Kustomer", "date": "7 February 2022", "question": "Describe a security incident and how did I handle it.", "answer": ["I described an incident and detailed the steps I took to identify, react, assemble team, remediate, assess and lessons learned. Less"]}, {"key": 503, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "TikTok", "date": "6 February 2022", "question": "Tell us about a time you went out of your way to fix a problem that no one else at the company had identified?", "answer": []}, {"key": 504, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "6 February 2022", "question": "Signed NDA about this for the interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 505, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Northrop Grumman", "date": "6 February 2022", "question": "How did I handle working with a difficult co-worker?", "answer": ["I said that communication with the worker was the key to having a better relationship to understand ways to work better together. Less"]}, {"key": 506, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "West End Diagnostic Imaging", "date": "5 February 2022", "question": "1)Tell me about yourself?\r\n2)How do you tackle situations under pressure?\r\n3)How do you resolve a conflict?\r\n4)Why do you want to work in Healthcare?\r\n5)Define the values you bring to the organization?", "answer": []}, {"key": 507, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Guild Education", "date": "4 February 2022", "question": "How would the candidate recommend that AWS be configured?", "answer": []}, {"key": 508, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Guild Education", "date": "4 February 2022", "question": "How  can a large enterprise apply the principle of least privilege and other best practice in their cloud environments?", "answer": []}, {"key": 509, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "RPM International", "date": "3 February 2022", "question": "Can you describe asymmetrical encryption?", "answer": []}, {"key": 510, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wise", "date": "3 February 2022", "question": "Why Wise? \r\nHow do you see yourself etc. \r\nThey share the documents in advance. \r\nFor the technical part, focus on best practices and your experiences.", "answer": []}, {"key": 511, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "2 February 2022", "question": "Related to technology which I have worked", "answer": []}, {"key": 512, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Bonusly", "date": "2 February 2022", "question": "Describe a situation where you made a mistake.  How did you handle it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 513, "position": "Azure Security Engineer", "company": "Mindtree", "date": "31 January 2022", "question": "When to connect two VM's if we have to enter the routing table?\r\nOn asking I am sorry can you please repeat the question again his reply was ok let's move to next:\r\nWhat is the use of Key Bolt?\r\nThird what scripting do you use in the routing table?", "answer": ["I was confused about the bolt word then immediately I recalled some people read V=B .\r\nRest all questions were above my IQ. Less"]}, {"key": 514, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adarma", "date": "31 January 2022", "question": "What do you like about us?", "answer": []}, {"key": 515, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sitel Group", "date": "30 January 2022", "question": "What are the three pillars of information security ?", "answer": ["Confidentiality, integrity and availability CIA", "Confidentiality, Integrity, Availability"]}, {"key": 516, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Radiometer", "date": "29 January 2022", "question": "Product security lifecycle, everything around. How will you work around with the security phase?", "answer": []}, {"key": 517, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "28 January 2022", "question": "Most questions were talking about challenges/problems solved at previous jobs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 518, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "TikTok", "date": "28 January 2022", "question": "Coding interview: To write a program to determine highest profitable stock.", "answer": []}, {"key": 519, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "28 January 2022", "question": "Write a custom memcpy function.", "answer": ["using malloc and iteratively copying the data from one object to another."]}, {"key": 520, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "ITC Secure", "date": "27 January 2022", "question": "They offered an online technical test, which had a good mix of networking and security questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 521, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Optimizely", "date": "27 January 2022", "question": "Can you tell me about project X on your resume?", "answer": []}, {"key": 522, "position": "Security Pre-sales Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "26 January 2022", "question": "Where would you look if you're looking for passwords on a Linux system?", "answer": []}, {"key": 523, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "HashiCorp", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "\u201cWhat is your biggest Weakness?\u201d\r\n\u201cWhy Hashicorp?\u201d", "answer": []}, {"key": 524, "position": "Cyber Security Risk Engineer", "company": "S&P Global", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "I was asked about my overall work  experience along with technical and scenario-based questions related to my role", "answer": []}, {"key": 525, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Equifax", "date": "25 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about your experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 526, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "DBS Bank", "date": "24 January 2022", "question": "What is the most challenging task you faced", "answer": []}, {"key": 527, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "24 January 2022", "question": "Basics of information security and nothing to worry about.", "answer": []}, {"key": 528, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Boeing", "date": "23 January 2022", "question": "how to work in team\r\none technical question", "answer": []}, {"key": 529, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "23 January 2022", "question": "Are you willing to relocate?", "answer": []}, {"key": 530, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Komodo Health", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "In the coding interview we covered getting information for AWS logs/data in two exercises", "answer": ["I wrote two functions, one for each exercise.  In the first exercise I added an additional case to cover that wasn't formally expressed in the sample dictionary of data but implied.  This was good because it opened an opportunity to discuss this case as well. Less"]}, {"key": 531, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "Questions about OWASP Top-10 . . .", "answer": []}, {"key": 532, "position": "Information Security Analyst, IT Business Analyst, and Network Systems Engineer", "company": "Cleco", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "What experience do you have with SAP or Workday?", "answer": []}, {"key": 533, "position": "Information Security Analyst, IT Business Analyst, and Network Systems Engineer", "company": "Cleco", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "What is your weakness and strengths?", "answer": []}, {"key": 534, "position": "Information Security Analyst, IT Business Analyst, and Network Systems Engineer", "company": "Cleco", "date": "20 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about your experience with programming.", "answer": []}, {"key": 535, "position": "Senior Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "Coinbase", "date": "19 January 2022", "question": "What happens when you go to Google and type in a search?\r\n\r\nWhat would you recommend for a simple web app for session management, and right now all it can do is login with a username and password?\r\n\r\nWhat are two ways your Coinbase Wallet could be vulnerable?", "answer": []}, {"key": 536, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Form3", "date": "18 January 2022", "question": "Networking, SDLC, Kubernetes, security fundamentals and aws cloud environment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 537, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "DOCK", "date": "18 January 2022", "question": "Quem \u00e9 voc\u00ea? \r\nO que voc\u00ea faz ?", "answer": ["Sou um estudante dedicado que aprende muito r\u00e1pido e procuro fazer tudo com muito esfor\u00e7o e dedica\u00e7\u00e3o Less"]}, {"key": 538, "position": "Security Tier II Systems Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "17 January 2022", "question": "In a high level details about devices functionality and path  packet flow regarding VPN and Firepower were asked.", "answer": ["Cannot reveal the answer as this is a personal technical answer, but I would say everything as according to books and functionalities is a proper answer. :) Less"]}, {"key": 539, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "17 January 2022", "question": "1. Searching and sorting algorithms\n2. Database concepts\n3. Java OOPs concepts\n4. Security related questions\n5. Projects\n6.Internship questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 540, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 January 2022", "question": "What's is the difference between synchronous encryption and asynchronous encryption? \r\n\r\nWhat steps do you take during an incident?", "answer": ["I believe you mean symmetric vs asymmetric"]}, {"key": 541, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Orlando Health", "date": "14 January 2022", "question": "Why is powershell better than the command line?", "answer": []}, {"key": 542, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Form3", "date": "13 January 2022", "question": "There was one small application, and task was to do code review.", "answer": []}, {"key": 543, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NTT Ltd.", "date": "12 January 2022", "question": "Network and security related question. e.g. IDS/IPS , stateful vs stateless firewall , SNMP , etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 544, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Shutterfly", "date": "12 January 2022", "question": "related to my previous work and technical  questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 545, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "10 January 2022", "question": "How many years of experience?", "answer": ["2"]}, {"key": 546, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ASAPP", "date": "8 January 2022", "question": "programar una lambda en aws usando servicios como sqs, borrar security groups no utlizados", "answer": []}, {"key": 547, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "8 January 2022", "question": "Questions about SQL Injection asked to write a script to count lines of code and a customer service-oriented question.", "answer": []}, {"key": 548, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "7 January 2022", "question": "what do you know about twilio?", "answer": []}, {"key": 549, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "7 January 2022", "question": "Apart from the technical questions, one that let me thinking is \"what would you do in this pandemic times where everyone is working remotely, so they could getting to know who you are or what you do\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 550, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "OpenTable", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Salary expectations\r\nExperience \r\nPast projects", "answer": []}, {"key": 551, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Miro", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Use your time to understand responsibilities and expectations from your role, the team is open to give clear answers. And of course, have a flashback of significant moments of your past job experiences before the interviews.", "answer": []}, {"key": 552, "position": "Android Security Engineer", "company": "Robinhood", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Does not apply to the situation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 553, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Describe what this code is doing/ what is the attacker trying to do to obfuscate this malware", "answer": []}, {"key": 554, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Describe what this code is doing/ what is the attacker trying to do to obfuscate this malware", "answer": []}, {"key": 555, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Outschool", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "What are the differences between SSL and TLS?", "answer": ["SSL 3.0 and TLS 1.0 are nearly identical. Otherwise, TLS is the newer standard and the one that should be followed. Less"]}, {"key": 556, "position": "IT Operations and Security Engineer", "company": "Arabesque ", "date": "6 January 2022", "question": "Why did you apply? What are you looking for in the role? etc; etc;", "answer": []}, {"key": 557, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Tempus Labs", "date": "5 January 2022", "question": "How is Serena Williams doing right now ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 558, "position": "Senior Security Systems Engineer", "company": "Blackboard", "date": "4 January 2022", "question": "how to secure cloud infraestucture?", "answer": []}, {"key": 559, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Edward Jones", "date": "3 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about a time you had to reach out to team members for assistance with a problem, and what you did with the help they provided.", "answer": []}, {"key": 560, "position": "Graduate Engineer Security Cyber Defense", "company": "ANZ", "date": "3 January 2022", "question": "Tell me about the projects you did.\nYour Hobbies\nWhy do u want to join ANZ.\nWhat field u r interested in", "answer": []}, {"key": 561, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HubSpot", "date": "2 January 2022", "question": "A lot of \"tell me about a time when...\" questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 562, "position": "Blockchain Security Engineer", "company": "CertiK", "date": "1 January 2022", "question": "Past experience, Have any questions for the interviewer", "answer": []}, {"key": 563, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Spiff", "date": "30 December 2021", "question": "Q: Tell me about yourself\nQ: Where do you see yourself in 1, 3, 5 years?\nQ: What specifically have you contributed to benefit your team/organization", "answer": ["Gave personal and professional background, specific details on career growth goals for 1, 3, and 5 years, and a specific example of how I contributed to organization success. Less"]}, {"key": 564, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "29 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are main components of \"secure\" in SSDLC, what 3 top things in terms of processes, controls or whatever would you recommend to start securing existing SDLC?", "answer": []}, {"key": 565, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "JupiterOne", "date": "28 December 2021", "question": "Have you worked with any data streaming tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 566, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "JupiterOne", "date": "28 December 2021", "question": "Have you used any IaC tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 567, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Comcast", "date": "27 December 2021", "question": "All about Endpoint Security and security technologies", "answer": []}, {"key": 568, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "23 December 2021", "question": "Tell me how a server connects to another server", "answer": []}, {"key": 569, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dave", "date": "23 December 2021", "question": "Q: How to integrate local domain and cloud provider credentials", "answer": []}, {"key": 570, "position": "Network Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Rakuten", "date": "22 December 2021", "question": "Asa packet flow and networking security concepts", "answer": ["Explained the packet flow through ASA firewall and was strong About the concepts mentioned in my resume Less"]}, {"key": 571, "position": "Junior Security Software Engineer", "company": "TSS Consultancy", "date": "21 December 2021", "question": "Owasp top 10, networking fundamental", "answer": []}, {"key": 572, "position": "Security Signature Engineer", "company": "Qualys", "date": "21 December 2021", "question": "Basically related to OWASP Top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 573, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Wildlife Studios", "date": "21 December 2021", "question": "How asymmetric encryption works?\nDescribe in details an SQL injections\nChoose any vulnerability you want  and fully describe it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 574, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Partners Group", "date": "17 December 2021", "question": "Some basics questions about IT security, DevOps with a case study about AWS + IT Security incident handling", "answer": []}, {"key": 575, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "17 December 2021", "question": "I will respect the NDA.\nQuestions are just as you would imagine as a security engineer. Don't hesitate to ask your recruiter for basic guidance on how to best prepare.", "answer": []}, {"key": 576, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "Asked to hack into a fake website.", "answer": []}, {"key": 577, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Vonage", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "General questions related to security, cloud, Linux", "answer": []}, {"key": 578, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "16 December 2021", "question": "Leetcode type Coding  challenge of medium - hard difficulty.", "answer": []}, {"key": 579, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "12 December 2021", "question": "Top 10 OWASP list and their description", "answer": []}, {"key": 580, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Web3 Foundation", "date": "12 December 2021", "question": "how would you start investigating a spoofed email (that seemed to come from the company's domain)?\r\nhow to perform transaction signing on a k8s cluster\r\nhow polkadot works and difference with bitcoin and ethereum", "answer": []}, {"key": 581, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Southern Company", "date": "11 December 2021", "question": "Tell us about a specific time when you had to help someone. What was the issue? and What was the outcome?", "answer": []}, {"key": 582, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Yell", "date": "11 December 2021", "question": "what are the stages you would go through when responding to a security incident", "answer": []}, {"key": 583, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 December 2021", "question": "Generic security engineering questions. No need to dig into the details", "answer": []}, {"key": 584, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "What is method overloading?\nWhat is method overriding?\nDifference between c and c++", "answer": []}, {"key": 585, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "Leetcode medium array related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 586, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Loginsoft", "date": "9 December 2021", "question": "All technical and practical questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 587, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 December 2021", "question": "Q: What do you want to do for the next few years in your career?\nQ: What's the most interesting security issue you found?", "answer": ["In general, good interview prep is key to crack the interviews."]}, {"key": 588, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "Nokia", "date": "8 December 2021", "question": "Focus was on my experience so far and what technologies I used before", "answer": []}, {"key": 589, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Doyen Infosolutions", "date": "7 December 2021", "question": "\"Say something about yourself......\" was the first question,\ngetting an overview of my resume, further questions were asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 590, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "3 December 2021", "question": "Basic networking knowledge, port numbers, appliance topology, and more.", "answer": []}, {"key": 591, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ITility", "date": "3 December 2021", "question": "Waarom heb je gekozen voor Itility", "answer": []}, {"key": 592, "position": "Devops Security Engineer", "company": "HubSpot", "date": "2 December 2021", "question": "They asked me to solve a specific question.", "answer": []}, {"key": 593, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Ebryx", "date": "1 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are the different network layer attacks I know of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 594, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Ebryx", "date": "1 December 2021", "question": "Q: What are the different network layer attacks I know of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 595, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MassMutual", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 596, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MassMutual", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 597, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "BitGo", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "The questions I wasn\u2019t able to answer clearly involved supply-chain attacks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 598, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "they ask whether I know anything about Huawei cloud", "answer": []}, {"key": 599, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "30 November 2021", "question": "they ask whether I know anything about Huawei cloud", "answer": []}, {"key": 600, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Cerebral (CA)", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "The interview did not actually happen", "answer": []}, {"key": 601, "position": "Senior Analyst Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "I was asked questions about real world implementation of Fourier series, a few things about computer network.", "answer": []}, {"key": 602, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "6sense", "date": "29 November 2021", "question": "I had total 10 rounds of interview, each round was based on the last round, interview had both theoretical as well as practical rounds. For security you have to be well versed in end to end security, including:\n1. DevOps security\n2. Application Security\n3. Infrastructure security\n4. Shell scripting.\n5. Penetration testing.\n6. AWS modules and security as a code.\n7. Policies and preventions.\n8. Coding - python, ansible, yara rules", "answer": ["Explain about each of these process as they ask about and I did well in them."]}, {"key": 603, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "28 November 2021", "question": "Code review, general security questions, AWS/cloud security, SSRF, secure design/threat modeling questions, behavior questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 604, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "TVS Motor Company", "date": "28 November 2021", "question": "Networking basic questions, TCP  UDP.", "answer": ["I answer all questions."]}, {"key": 605, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Conductor", "date": "26 November 2021", "question": "How would you act in case of incident?", "answer": []}, {"key": 606, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 November 2021", "question": "OWASP 10 (xss, csrf)\ncryptography(explain PKI, diffie hellman)\nlots of behavioral questions for more than 50% of the time.\nCoding round was pretty simple, asked for a simple loop, no harder than leetcode easy", "answer": []}, {"key": 607, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Hexaware Technologies", "date": "25 November 2021", "question": "Azure  Cloud Security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 608, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ID.me", "date": "24 November 2021", "question": "Describe a situation where you failed and what did you do to handle it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 609, "position": "Software Engineer (Security Platform)", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "24 November 2021", "question": "No real questions, simply saying i dont meet the criteria of hiring and thats about it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 610, "position": "Cloud Security Operations Engineer", "company": "2nd Watch", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Pen testing phases/stages \nExplain ARP poisoning\nBasic security questions (CIA, hashing,etc)", "answer": []}, {"key": 611, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Kajabi", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Application Security Engineer questions, web app vulnerability management, code review, security's role in SDLC.", "answer": []}, {"key": 612, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Bridgewater Associates", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "They asked questions that were on point with the job description, there were no \"gotcha\" type questions. The recruiter was very clear as to what to expect when speaking with other team members.", "answer": []}, {"key": 613, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Reddit", "date": "23 November 2021", "question": "Nothing to do with cloud/security engineering at all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 614, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "CyberCoders", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Recruiter asked about experience in each of the job requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 615, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Describe why you think diversity is important.", "answer": ["I virtue-signaled with my typical answer that let them know I really do consider harmonious diversity a strength.  (And I do.) Less"]}, {"key": 616, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "19 November 2021", "question": "Describe why you think diversity is important.", "answer": ["I virtue-signaled with my typical answer that let them know I really do consider harmonious diversity a strength.  (And I do.) Less"]}, {"key": 617, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "Question about a project from your resume and then build upon the technical aspects of it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 618, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "Question about a project from your resume and then build upon the technical aspects of it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 619, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Amadeus", "date": "18 November 2021", "question": "How does Diffie Hellman work?\nIP subnetting\nChange management process and incident recovery experience\nFirewall and proxy experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 620, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "17 November 2021", "question": "Q: Choose one of the OWASP top ten and describe it in detail.", "answer": []}, {"key": 621, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "Talk about your experience with McAfee products.", "answer": []}, {"key": 622, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "Have you ever work with requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 623, "position": "Information Security Systems Engineer (ISSE)", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "16 November 2021", "question": "What is your knowledge on agile projects?", "answer": []}, {"key": 624, "position": "Senior Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "15 November 2021", "question": "What vulns currently exist with Netflix?", "answer": ["Wasn\u2019t too sure, mentioned potential DDOS/account theft"]}, {"key": 625, "position": "Senior Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "15 November 2021", "question": "What is currently wrong with SOCs right now and how would you improve them?", "answer": ["Mentioned SOAR / repetitive tasks / automation"]}, {"key": 626, "position": "Senior Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "15 November 2021", "question": "How would you configure a SIEM to filter out a large amount of events?", "answer": ["Mentioned data models, lookup tables, high IOPs, filtering at ingestion layer, filtering at script layer, etc. Less"]}, {"key": 627, "position": "Senior Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "15 November 2021", "question": "Did you apply for this position? :( / What is your ideal role?", "answer": ["Yes"]}, {"key": 628, "position": "Senior Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "15 November 2021", "question": "How would you get metrics to measure the performance of the whole team?", "answer": ["Gave him quantitative and qualitative answers. He didn't like either answer.", "Look at KPI (key performing indicators) such as spend vs budget, track the volume of changes impacting deliverables, etc. Promote change, get innovated and strategically plan to to avoid spending over budget and Avoiding bottlenecks to name a few. Less"]}, {"key": 629, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "14 November 2021", "question": "Deep understanding of common classes of product security vulnerabilities and attack/ defence methodologies.\nknowledge of the security development lifecycle and threat modelling process", "answer": []}, {"key": 630, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "BigID", "date": "12 November 2021", "question": "The BigID interview process did have some technical aspects for the role in question, but it was mostly about getting a feel for the culture, and whether or not I would be a good fit for them, and vice versa.", "answer": []}, {"key": 631, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Unified Healthcare Group", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Talk about the Owasp top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 632, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hotstar", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Most of questions were scenario-based and not routine questions about attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 633, "position": "Security Software Developer", "company": "SafeBreach", "date": "11 November 2021", "question": "Home excersize is a good representation for the job requirements and entailed implementing a small PoC of an attack on an existing windows system mechanism.\nInterview contained several questions around networking and protocols.", "answer": []}, {"key": 634, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Redox, Inc.", "date": "10 November 2021", "question": "1. What are your personal principles and strategies to reduce vulnerabilities introduced into production?\n2. How do you stay up to date with new/emerging technology?\n\nOther than that, it was fairly straightforward.  No coding, all situational (Describe a time where...).  Be ready for an ongoing conversation, and diving deeper into each of your answers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 635, "position": "Product Security Software Engineer", "company": "Varian Medical Systems", "date": "10 November 2021", "question": "How do you tell if a vulnerability has high impact?", "answer": []}, {"key": 636, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "In my opinion expected salary doesn't fit their requirement", "answer": ["The main problem is that, nobody didn't gave me except reason why I didn't selected Less"]}, {"key": 637, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AGIO", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "Questions about SIEM, XDR, incident response", "answer": []}, {"key": 638, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NIKE", "date": "9 November 2021", "question": "Qualities of a good manager", "answer": []}, {"key": 639, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "1Password", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Explain Encryption, Hashing, and encoding.", "answer": ["Know what they are and what they are used for protect."]}, {"key": 640, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "How would you protect a house from outsiders?", "answer": ["Go through this systematically and logically"]}, {"key": 641, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Paran\u00e1 Banco", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Cite algum desafio.", "answer": []}, {"key": 642, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cognite", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Risk assessment process and life cy", "answer": []}, {"key": 643, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cognite", "date": "8 November 2021", "question": "Risk assessment process and life cy", "answer": []}, {"key": 644, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HCLTech", "date": "6 November 2021", "question": "tools you have worked on mostly on ATP. and how to whitelist and all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 645, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "6 November 2021", "question": "Implement a linked list and then implement an algorithm that says if theres a loop.\nThere was another one but I forgot.", "answer": []}, {"key": 646, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Trulioo", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "1. One of encryption method algorithm\r\n2. Hashing method\r\n3. Live coding challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 647, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "There were code reviews and questions about how to design secure environments", "answer": []}, {"key": 648, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "FloQast", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "What is a CSRF attack?", "answer": ["Wasn\u2019t asked about how to prevent it."]}, {"key": 649, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Beyond Identity", "date": "4 November 2021", "question": "Web security, DEP, ASLR, SAML, OIDC, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 650, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dell Technologies", "date": "3 November 2021", "question": "Very basic cybersecurity questions, networking, etc...", "answer": []}, {"key": 651, "position": "Staff Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Very Good Security", "date": "3 November 2021", "question": "You receive a security alert for activity on a system, how do you go about triaging, investigating, and then responding to the incident. \r\n\r\nBasically asked to detail different aspects of the IR lifecycle.", "answer": []}, {"key": 652, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What is perfect forward secrecy in the TLS protocol?", "answer": []}, {"key": 653, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What is the difference between strongly-typed and weakly-typed programming languages and can you give an example?", "answer": []}, {"key": 654, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Q: What kind of cryptography TLS protocol uses (asymmetric-key, symmetric-key, both)?", "answer": []}, {"key": 655, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ByteDance", "date": "2 November 2021", "question": "Gave a sample post request and ask to explain on the possible exploitation", "answer": []}, {"key": 656, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Clark (Germany)", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "Introduce yourself.\nPast Experience. \nTechnologies I have worked on.", "answer": []}, {"key": 657, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Kiratech", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "Chi \u00e8 per te il DevOps", "answer": []}, {"key": 658, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "1 November 2021", "question": "What is somsth you have learned recently and how did you apply it to the workplace.", "answer": []}, {"key": 659, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Nuna", "date": "30 October 2021", "question": "The interviews were nicely divided and not repetetive. They tried to know me not only technically but also had beavioral questions.\r\n\r\nInitial interviews were about my experience, my current role, what are my interests, why am I looking for a change, etc.\r\n\r\nSome of the technological questions were on topics such as:\r\nOIDC, SAML, SSO, AWS, S3, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 660, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "27 October 2021", "question": "as usual first will be 2 technical rounds and after that HR round", "answer": []}, {"key": 661, "position": "Security Operations Engineer - SOE", "company": "Blend", "date": "26 October 2021", "question": "How do you match Blends culture?", "answer": []}, {"key": 662, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "25 October 2021", "question": "Know and understand the company's values and how it applies to you.", "answer": []}, {"key": 663, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Qorvo", "date": "25 October 2021", "question": "Do you have any experience with SOAR?", "answer": []}, {"key": 664, "position": "Cloud Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Teradata", "date": "22 October 2021", "question": "Can you tell me of a project that you recently worked on that you are proud of?", "answer": ["I described one of the projects that I had recently worked on."]}, {"key": 665, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "20 October 2021", "question": "Terraform policies for collaboration\nAnsible roles \nScript challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 666, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Honeywell", "date": "20 October 2021", "question": "Tell us why you would like to work for Honeywell and why you are interested in this role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 667, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Unqork", "date": "19 October 2021", "question": "Tell me about how you would approach a web app for testing.", "answer": []}, {"key": 668, "position": "Security Compliance Engineer", "company": "Typeform", "date": "19 October 2021", "question": "Why I was in the hiring process (context: I had joined the previous company just 4,5 months before).", "answer": ["I did a research about Typeform's history, services, values, philosophy, etc., and not just the position, but the company itself motivated me to try to join Typeform. Less"]}, {"key": 669, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CENSUS", "date": "17 October 2021", "question": "Technical challenge in C, memory allocation questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 670, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "ExamWorks", "date": "16 October 2021", "question": "What are your salary expectations?", "answer": []}, {"key": 671, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "15 October 2021", "question": "What is your cyber security related experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 672, "position": "Senior Infrastructure & Security Engineer", "company": "Stoke Therapuetics", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "They asked about my experiences with IT security compliance issues.", "answer": ["I explained my experience with preparing for a SOC 2 Type 2 audit."]}, {"key": 673, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Figma", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "Coding Challenge to be completed in less than 2 hours requiring research and mathematical algorithms.", "answer": []}, {"key": 674, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "What are the  different types of encryption.", "answer": ["Hash passwords with salt.\n\nNever store in clear text \n\nNever allow passwords within connection strings.\n\nUse a key vault for all authentication processes. Less"]}, {"key": 675, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "The second round just go through a simple code interview (sorting) and cyber security-related questions (identify CVE etc).", "answer": []}, {"key": 676, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "Fully Technical Security related question", "answer": []}, {"key": 677, "position": "Sales Engineer ( Trust and Security)", "company": "Bugcrowd", "date": "14 October 2021", "question": "your role in sales cycle", "answer": ["answer thru experience"]}, {"key": 678, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "CenturyLink", "date": "13 October 2021", "question": "TCP/IP overview, how does TLS work, what is Linux shadow file for, how does XSS work, what is DNS, what is BGP, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 679, "position": "Senior Software Engineer (Security)", "company": "Coinbase", "date": "12 October 2021", "question": "Describe what happens when I type 'google.com' into a web browser.", "answer": []}, {"key": 680, "position": "Fire and Security Service Engineer", "company": "Reflexis Systems", "date": "11 October 2021", "question": "What size of systems have you worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 681, "position": "Senior IT Security Engineer", "company": "GEODIS", "date": "7 October 2021", "question": "What is your salary expectation for this position based on your experience?", "answer": ["I didn't provide a hard number, because I don't have all the information available to accurately assess the value of a compensation package. Less"]}, {"key": 682, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "7 October 2021", "question": "General security questions, environments and technologies I worked with.", "answer": []}, {"key": 683, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Was asked to indentify real-word vulnerabilities in prints of source code.", "answer": []}, {"key": 684, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Tell me About yourself\nWhere do you see yourself in 5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 685, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Deep technical questions on offensive security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 686, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Deep technical questions on offensive security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 687, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Providence Health Care", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Authentication resumed based questions regarding my skills", "answer": []}, {"key": 688, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "Herjavec Group", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Work experience with practical application?", "answer": []}, {"key": 689, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Saint-Gobain", "date": "6 October 2021", "question": "Working of the firewalls and proxies", "answer": []}, {"key": 690, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "Amazon", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "LP, Threat Modeling, Pen testing scenario, code review, PKI", "answer": ["Leadership Principles of Amazon", "what's LP?"]}, {"key": 691, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "Specific questions about the OSI Model and how to analyze security logs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 692, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sourcegraph", "date": "5 October 2021", "question": "Describe a situation in which conflict occurred and how you addressed it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 693, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "4 October 2021", "question": "What was a time you dealt with a stressful situation? How did you overcome this?", "answer": ["Discussed a specific customer support engagement that was severely escalated. Addressed the issue with clear communication and expectations until resolution. Less"]}, {"key": 694, "position": "Sr Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "4 October 2021", "question": "Basic security questions, like TCP handshakes, how does ssh work, what tools used !!\n\nHave you done threat model and code review etc. \n\n80% of the interview was businessy questions such as: \"tell me about a time you took a risk at work\" etc.\n\n(I am not sure why a technical position didn't have more technical questions and less leadership questions )", "answer": []}, {"key": 695, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "1 October 2021", "question": "The interview questions were mostly open-ended, which gives candidates a chance to show their strengths.", "answer": []}, {"key": 696, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "1 October 2021", "question": "The interview questions were mostly open-ended, which gives candidates a chance to show their strengths.", "answer": []}, {"key": 697, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Frame.io", "date": "30 September 2021", "question": "1- Describe the most innovative project I lead \n2- How would my team members describe me \n3- AWS Cloud Security questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 698, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Backbase", "date": "30 September 2021", "question": "What would you recommend to mitigate risk of MITM attack on a web application?", "answer": []}, {"key": 699, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "cannot discuss due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 700, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "The technical questions included designing some real life feature from a security perspective.", "answer": []}, {"key": 701, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Klarna", "date": "29 September 2021", "question": "general security questions about DDoS, cryptography", "answer": []}, {"key": 702, "position": "Software Engineer - Security", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "A junior engineer asked me a few cultural fit questions and then dived into system design for 40 min. He asked me to design Doordash. + Uber backend, \r\n\r\nHad a good conversation. But i felt the interviewer did not have much experience. He knew the basic stuff of NoSQL vs RDS, Caching, LB etc.\r\n\r\nOverall the tech screen was good.", "answer": []}, {"key": 703, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Communications", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Technicals fundamental questions were asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 704, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Communications", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Senario based questions were asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 705, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Basics of networking, cybersecurity, and questions based on the CV.", "answer": []}, {"key": 706, "position": "Security Research Engineer", "company": "Lojas Riachuelo", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Related to security question it was", "answer": ["Uses of stack"]}, {"key": 707, "position": "Software Developer - Security Team", "company": "Grab", "date": "28 September 2021", "question": "Online Test:\r\nIt comprised of 3 problem solving coding questions, testing knowledge of typical DS/Algos. Time allotted for the test is sufficient.\r\nCoding: Standard DS/Algos are sufficient to come up with the sol.", "answer": []}, {"key": 708, "position": "Network Security/SASE Engineer", "company": "Aruba Networks", "date": "27 September 2021", "question": "C programming (Traverse a Binary Search Tree, Insertion in Binary Tree, Best day to buy and Sell stock in Linear Time), System Design: File hosting for 100-500 people", "answer": []}, {"key": 709, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Ocado Group", "date": "27 September 2021", "question": "Technical questions about encryption and data protection", "answer": []}, {"key": 710, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "26 September 2021", "question": "Cloudflare magic transit and how it works", "answer": []}, {"key": 711, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Microland", "date": "25 September 2021", "question": "What is the ospf cost", "answer": ["It's 110"]}, {"key": 712, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "24 September 2021", "question": "The questions were related to dev ops and programming.", "answer": []}, {"key": 713, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "24 September 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 714, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Eyeo", "date": "23 September 2021", "question": "Do you think a 2FA implementation is a perfect/unbreakable solution for all the problems considering authentication? Could there be issues regarding 2FAs?", "answer": []}, {"key": 715, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CSG", "date": "23 September 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself and about your work experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 716, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Movate", "date": "22 September 2021", "question": "Ccna, tcp ip, routing switching", "answer": []}, {"key": 717, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GSK", "date": "20 September 2021", "question": "Technical question related to understanding of cybersecurity, networking & firewall.", "answer": []}, {"key": 718, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "20 September 2021", "question": "How would I empty an airplane filled with jelly beans.", "answer": []}, {"key": 719, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "EY", "date": "18 September 2021", "question": "Comment vous voyez vous dans 5 ans chez EY?", "answer": []}, {"key": 720, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cognizant Technology Solutions", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "Introduce about yourself, about the projects done in college.", "answer": []}, {"key": 721, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BayCare Health System", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 722, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Navi Technologies", "date": "17 September 2021", "question": "How to secure communication between AWS and GCP", "answer": []}, {"key": 723, "position": "Engineer II - Security", "company": "Verizon", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "What is Second Order SQLi?", "answer": []}, {"key": 724, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sdgc", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "what is OWASP TOP 10 ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 725, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Banyan Cloud", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "what is called as web application ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 726, "position": "Summer: Software, Platform Or Security Engineer", "company": "bp", "date": "16 September 2021", "question": "What interests you in working in software development?", "answer": ["I got into coding during the summer of 2020 when my internship had been cancelled, and I started to love working on my own mini projects while learning how to code at the same time. I like the work flow of designing, drafting, troubleshooting and then iterating on your work to add features and make it more efficient. Each design challenge is like a puzzle that I get great enjoyment from solving. Working on bigger, more collaborative projects would be beneficial to me as I could improve my understanding of best principles for designing the architecture of a software. Less"]}, {"key": 727, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Esper", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "1. Gave two coding questions and asked for code optimization\n2. Have you worked on firewall", "answer": []}, {"key": 728, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "Tell me about your experience and background", "answer": []}, {"key": 729, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Diligent", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "What do you like to do outside of security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 730, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "15 September 2021", "question": "What's one of your greatest challenges.", "answer": []}, {"key": 731, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "what is scalability in cloud?", "answer": ["scalability is one of the main moto of cloud providers. we can easily scale in or scale out our resources based on our own requirements. Less"]}, {"key": 732, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Blu", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "Me fale um pouco sobre suas experi\u00eancias?\nConte o que voc\u00ea espera para essa vaga?\nQuais s\u00e3o suas motiva\u00e7\u00f5es?", "answer": []}, {"key": 733, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Reddit", "date": "14 September 2021", "question": "There were no technical questions, just \"why do you want to work at Reddit\", or \"how would you explain XYZ to someone\". Questions similar to that.", "answer": []}, {"key": 734, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ActioNet", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "CISSP Credentials are required for this role, where are you in your CPE cycle?", "answer": []}, {"key": 735, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Locuz Enterprise Solutions", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "Please go through the fundamental concepts of Network and Network Security domain.", "answer": []}, {"key": 736, "position": "\u200bSecurity Research Software Developer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "13 September 2021", "question": "Basic OOP questions in python.", "answer": []}, {"key": 737, "position": "Security Engineer - Red Team", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 September 2021", "question": "Asked trivia questions like \u201cwhat is the underlying file type of office macros\u201d and \u201cwhat is the file type extension of modern office files\u201d", "answer": ["Many similar trivia questions were asked"]}, {"key": 738, "position": "Security Engineer - Red Team", "company": "TikTok", "date": "11 September 2021", "question": "Asked detailed questions about windows API and exploit development. Must know exact function names off the top of your head", "answer": ["Seemed like they were looking for hobbyist malware developers and 0day hunters"]}, {"key": 739, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Marqeta", "date": "10 September 2021", "question": "any failed projects that worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 740, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "10 September 2021", "question": "Knowledge on ISO 27001 standard and specifications", "answer": []}, {"key": 741, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Westcon-Comstor", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "What are your interests in security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 742, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Different kinds of XSS and how to fix them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 743, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Philip Morris International", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Difference between SAST and DAST from vulnerability identification perspective? Limitations in both approaches.", "answer": []}, {"key": 744, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "GeniusRx", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "The 2 ladies in HR kept talking about the company history and \"personalities\" but had no questions.  The only question was \"do you have any question for me\" to which  I asked a couple of questions and both ladies were completely clueless.", "answer": []}, {"key": 745, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "MyFitnessPal", "date": "9 September 2021", "question": "Describe a time when a project had a major hurdle and how did you overcome that hurdle.", "answer": ["I gave an honest answer about a problem with interdepartmental relationships"]}, {"key": 746, "position": "Lead Security Engineer, Cyber CloudOps", "company": "Circle Internet Financial", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "Do you know how to write in golang?", "answer": ["No.. why would I."]}, {"key": 747, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Safelite AutoGlass", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "Mostly typical interview question for a position like this.", "answer": ["I thin I answered them well."]}, {"key": 748, "position": "Software Developer In Security", "company": "Rakuten", "date": "8 September 2021", "question": "given a sequence of binary numbers from 1 to n, what is the result of applying the xor operation on each  eg. 0001 xor 0010 xor 0011 xor ....", "answer": ["# Python 3 Program to find\n# XOR of numbers from 1 to n.\ndef computeXOR(n) :\n \n    # Modulus operator are expensive\n    # on most of the computers. n &amp; 3\n    # will be equivalent to n % 4.\n \n    # if n is multiple of 4\n    if n % 4 == 0 :\n        return n\n \n    # If n % 4 gives remainder 1\n    if n % 4 == 1 :\n        return 1\n \n    # If n%4 gives remainder 2\n    if n % 4 == 2 :\n        return n + 1\n \n    # If n%4 gives remainder 3\n    return 0 Less"]}, {"key": 749, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Database related questions on RDBMS and SQL queries", "answer": []}, {"key": 750, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "VIEWNEXT", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Por que te cambias? \nQue funciones realizas? \nDisponibilidad", "answer": []}, {"key": 751, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Technology related questions and domain related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 752, "position": "Software Security Developer", "company": "Helcim", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "what would you do in some specific situations to solve a problem?\nDescribe a past experience when you had succeeded?\netc", "answer": []}, {"key": 753, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Trade Republic", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet", "answer": []}, {"key": 754, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Bitpanda", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "How would you secure a distinct workload in the Cloud?", "answer": []}, {"key": 755, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Security Research Labs", "date": "7 September 2021", "question": "whats your name ?\r\nwhat is your current job?\r\nwhat is your specialy skill ?", "answer": ["my name is xxxxx\r\nmy current jobs is xxxxx\r\nmy specialy skill is xxxxx"]}, {"key": 756, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "6 September 2021", "question": "basic of information security\nhow to solve any test case like virus break out", "answer": []}, {"key": 757, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "5 September 2021", "question": "What is your day to day and then go in detail about it.", "answer": ["Explained end to end process I follow."]}, {"key": 758, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ParkNow", "date": "4 September 2021", "question": "Tell us about your experience as security engineer? some questions about python and AWS", "answer": []}, {"key": 759, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Northern Lights Technology Development", "date": "4 September 2021", "question": "What is click jacking ?", "answer": ["Its the most easiest question in web security."]}, {"key": 760, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Nones", "date": "3 September 2021", "question": "is there any vacancy available?", "answer": []}, {"key": 761, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Harness", "date": "2 September 2021", "question": "A real time scenario about the secrets management and how could it be efficiently be resolved was asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 762, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "eClerx", "date": "1 September 2021", "question": "Basics intervuew questions of technology", "answer": []}, {"key": 763, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Silicon Valley Bank", "date": "31 August 2021", "question": "Basics of OWASP\nTools used like-Appscan,Burpsuite\nXSS, CSRF, File upload\nEncryption, Hashing", "answer": []}, {"key": 764, "position": "Devops Security Engineer", "company": "NowPow", "date": "31 August 2021", "question": "How have you worked on securing CI/CD pipelines", "answer": []}, {"key": 765, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Do you have experience with Spring?", "answer": []}, {"key": 766, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Canonical", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Beginning in your high school years, through university and into your career, what have you done that you consider exceptional?\r\nWhy do you want to work for Canonical?\r\nHow are you involved in Open Source software (did you even contributed)?\r\nWhat are your strengths as a software engineer?\r\nLooks like you have been able to gather broad experiences in programming languages - how good would you rate your skills especially in Python and Go?", "answer": []}, {"key": 767, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No questions .. ... .", "answer": []}, {"key": 768, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No Questions ....", "answer": []}, {"key": 769, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Aigent", "date": "30 August 2021", "question": "Yes or No questions with out any questions that could evaluate your skill ,experiences , attitude ..etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 770, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ola", "date": "29 August 2021", "question": "He just asked 50 + questions security terms in 1 hr time kind of definition based.  No scenario based question etc.", "answer": ["I answered what i knew , but was not happy that he has shut his webcam."]}, {"key": 771, "position": "Vehicle Security Engineer", "company": "Nuro", "date": "28 August 2021", "question": "What do you hope to gain out of this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 772, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "27 August 2021", "question": "Take me through your career from the start to present day and how you got to where you are today.", "answer": []}, {"key": 773, "position": "Senior Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Truveta", "date": "26 August 2021", "question": "Walk through penetration testing scenario the interviewer was describing\r\nWhat is your proudest professional career moment\r\nWhat is a mistake you have made in your career/environment\r\nWhy are you switching jobs", "answer": []}, {"key": 774, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "26 August 2021", "question": "How much do you know about this job position.", "answer": []}, {"key": 775, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Meta", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "No questions were asked during technical round of interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 776, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "What are the steps and actions to containing a spillage?", "answer": []}, {"key": 777, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "25 August 2021", "question": "They were very interested in my cloud background given the focus on their cloud family of products, CloudGuard.", "answer": []}, {"key": 778, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AT&T", "date": "24 August 2021", "question": "What is your experience in configuring log collection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 779, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Snyk", "date": "23 August 2021", "question": "Tell me about how you've handled an incident and what you learned from it", "answer": []}, {"key": 780, "position": "Security Network Engineer", "company": "Schroders", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "how do you configure vpc in nexus switches?", "answer": []}, {"key": 781, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Rivian", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "It was more about what my relevant experience was in relation to the job I was applying for.", "answer": []}, {"key": 782, "position": "Automotive Security Developer", "company": "HARMAN", "date": "20 August 2021", "question": "1. About working of  SHE Specification  : How SHE Messages M1,M2,M3 are processed by ECU ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 783, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Apex Systems", "date": "19 August 2021", "question": "Typical questions for the field.  They did throw in questions not listed as part of the job description", "answer": ["Described my experiences working in the field"]}, {"key": 784, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "19 August 2021", "question": "Describe the difference in Hashing and Cryptography.", "answer": []}, {"key": 785, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "RiverSafe", "date": "19 August 2021", "question": "General networking and security questions mostly", "answer": []}, {"key": 786, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Checkmarx", "date": "18 August 2021", "question": "The questions were marked as classified.", "answer": []}, {"key": 787, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "17 August 2021", "question": "Experience with programming and knowledge with algorithms and their use cases is needed.", "answer": []}, {"key": 788, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Klarna", "date": "17 August 2021", "question": "Never asked any questions. Link to a brain teaser quiz. Never got any farther.", "answer": []}, {"key": 789, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zendesk", "date": "15 August 2021", "question": "Those should be some non-necessarily technical questions, but I signed an NDA, so I cannot tell. That is how you keep your company secrets safe after all, right?", "answer": []}, {"key": 790, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Emerson", "date": "15 August 2021", "question": "Q: Please run through your resume and tell me about yourself.", "answer": []}, {"key": 791, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Exabeam", "date": "12 August 2021", "question": "Technical discussion mostly about linux and troubleshooting.", "answer": []}, {"key": 792, "position": "Senior Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "GitHub", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work at GitHub", "answer": []}, {"key": 793, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adobe", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Resume related questions\nSort an array of numbers in words in numerical order", "answer": []}, {"key": 794, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solaris Group", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Are you comfortable with Linux", "answer": []}, {"key": 795, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Pearson", "date": "11 August 2021", "question": "Explain the difference between a static and non-static inner class.", "answer": []}, {"key": 796, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Huawei Technologies", "date": "10 August 2021", "question": "Read about counting sort in 3 minutes, and implement it based on your understanding.", "answer": []}, {"key": 797, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "HedgeServ", "date": "9 August 2021", "question": "There were no specific technical questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 798, "position": "Client Software Engineer, Security & Cryptography", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "The coding assignment was to design a program that sorts teams for a coding competition", "answer": []}, {"key": 799, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Seattle City Light", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "What is CIA?\nWhat type of IDS did you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 800, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "OCBC Bank", "date": "7 August 2021", "question": "Tell us more about the internship project you have done in the final year?", "answer": []}, {"key": 801, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "HSBC", "date": "6 August 2021", "question": "All questions were asked based on my experience and real time case studies. Mainly related to Risk Assessment, Cyber security management, compliance etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 802, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Wikimedia Foundation", "date": "5 August 2021", "question": "Crappy questions that I don't bother to remember", "answer": []}, {"key": 803, "position": "Entry Level Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "General Atomics", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "Cookie cutter interview. Tell me about yourself.", "answer": []}, {"key": 804, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is SQL injection? How do you mitigate it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 805, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is Router vs Switch?", "answer": []}, {"key": 806, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Akamai", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "What is Content Delivery Network", "answer": ["A CDN (Content Delivery Network) is a highly-distributed platform of servers that helps minimize delays in loading web page content by reducing the physical distance between the server and the user. This helps users around the world view the same high-quality content without slow loading times. Less"]}, {"key": 807, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lindsay Corporation", "date": "4 August 2021", "question": "Can you describe what your ideal incident response process would entail?", "answer": []}, {"key": 808, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "3 August 2021", "question": "Questions on Networking and and operating systems.", "answer": []}, {"key": 809, "position": "Sr. Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "Using a script of sudo code how would you create a report from two separate log files to concatenate the files together.", "answer": ["Pull data from log file 1 into a data set.  Pull data from log file 2 into a different data set.  Export results of data set 1 + data set 2. Less"]}, {"key": 810, "position": "Graduate Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "How would I react if everyday I had a different task?", "answer": []}, {"key": 811, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Eyeo", "date": "2 August 2021", "question": "They asked behavioral questions and technical ones.", "answer": []}, {"key": 812, "position": "Security Services Engineer", "company": "CyberArk", "date": "1 August 2021", "question": "Why I want to work for CyberArk.", "answer": []}, {"key": 813, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HelloFresh", "date": "1 August 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself and your experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 814, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "We expect you to \u201cfail\u201d when you\u2019re new. Describe a time when you failed and what you did after.", "answer": []}, {"key": 815, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "You\u2019re the brand new CISO of a small company and want to secure your endpoints. What is your first step?", "answer": []}, {"key": 816, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "Describe the difference between an IPS, IDS and Firewall; how would you use them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 817, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "we45", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "Some basic assignment on web app pentesting", "answer": []}, {"key": 818, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Citizen (NY)", "date": "30 July 2021", "question": "What Products are you familiar with?  Do you have any experience with Google Cloud Engine?", "answer": []}, {"key": 819, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Optimizely", "date": "29 July 2021", "question": "What is your experience around SIEM integration?", "answer": []}, {"key": 820, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Frontline Education", "date": "29 July 2021", "question": "About my work and security related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 821, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Skedulo", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "Describe your experience with risk assessment and compliance frameworks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 822, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DISH", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "Why do you want to work with Dish? Why are you fit dor this role", "answer": []}, {"key": 823, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "NetSentries Technologies", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "Normal questions related to Penetration Testing", "answer": ["Easy"]}, {"key": 824, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wave", "date": "28 July 2021", "question": "It started from General Behavioral Questions to technical one which included understanding of DevSecOps, Cloud Security etc. and Team player, Contribution based question", "answer": []}, {"key": 825, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Genesys", "date": "25 July 2021", "question": "Threat Modelling, SAST,DAST,Pentest,\nOWASP top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 826, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tyro Payments", "date": "24 July 2021", "question": "Python Coding exam to perform certain functions", "answer": ["Coding submission"]}, {"key": 827, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sennovate", "date": "24 July 2021", "question": "For my academic project details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 828, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "23 July 2021", "question": "Security, Python, Automation, Detection, Networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 829, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Scenario based questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 830, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Past experience and projects dive deep", "answer": []}, {"key": 831, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Design of security architecture", "answer": []}, {"key": 832, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Design: Given a certain scenario, where and what security controls would you implement?", "answer": []}, {"key": 833, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Fireblocks", "date": "22 July 2021", "question": "Projects and past experience questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 834, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Security hardening configurations for operating systems", "answer": []}, {"key": 835, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Email Security features and services for protecting email servers", "answer": []}, {"key": 836, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Arla Foods", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "What kind of solutions we can use for controlling users access to Cloud Apps", "answer": []}, {"key": 837, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Postman", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "What is this ___ attack and How do you prevent it?", "answer": ["____ -&gt; I was asked about CSRF and XSS. I gave an example while explaining the vulnerability.I spoke about CORS policy, CSRF tokens etc... Less"]}, {"key": 838, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Red Ventures", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "How would you automate security scanning? Describe a role that involved that automation?", "answer": ["Provided about 4 different examples how I was currently conducting automation via Burp, zap, qualys and snyk Less"]}, {"key": 839, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Collective Health", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "Why are you looking for a change?", "answer": []}, {"key": 840, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "SpaceX", "date": "20 July 2021", "question": "How much do you know about different encryption schemes?", "answer": []}, {"key": 841, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Paycom", "date": "19 July 2021", "question": "Tell me about the OWASP top 10", "answer": []}, {"key": 842, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Grab", "date": "15 July 2021", "question": "Basic security questions and process \r\nCould not understand most of the terms", "answer": []}, {"key": 843, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "PwC", "date": "13 July 2021", "question": "What is cybersecurity?\r\nHave you done any relevant job?", "answer": []}, {"key": 844, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "13 July 2021", "question": "Recall a time you failed at something?", "answer": []}, {"key": 845, "position": "Lead Application Security Engineer", "company": "S&P Global", "date": "12 July 2021", "question": "1. They come with python project, asked to identify bugs in python code\r\n2. They run the code and asked to how you enumerate application manually without using 3. nmap, dirbuster nor any automation tool.\r\n4. Explain about Json interoperatable attack\r\n5. Explain about Dependency confusion attack\r\n6. Explain about printspool attack \r\n7. Explain how can get RFI with only having LFI vulnerability in php application\r\n8. Explain about deserialization attack\r\n9. Explain what checks you perform on windows machine to exploit privilege escalation attack\r\n10. How you will perform pivoting attacks", "answer": []}, {"key": 846, "position": "Information Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Shaw Industries", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "Asked about the star method and my experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 847, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "Too many tech questions in the get-to-know-you round. That too from googling.", "answer": []}, {"key": 848, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "AceTeam Networks", "date": "9 July 2021", "question": "tell me about yourself\ncareer plan\nstrength/weakness\nOSI layers\nProblem and solution on WiFi issues\nWiFi 6 questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 849, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Hands-on knowledge, scenarios, and code reading.", "answer": ["Through experience."]}, {"key": 850, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iOPEX Technologies", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Self introduction, questions regarding our project, have you worked on Iot technology?", "answer": []}, {"key": 851, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Codility with three different questions. 90 min.", "answer": []}, {"key": 852, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "Design a calculator and do some coding.", "answer": ["Use a tree"]}, {"key": 853, "position": "Software Engineer - Cloud Security", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "8 July 2021", "question": "coding an iterator by yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 854, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Trend Micro Inc.", "date": "7 July 2021", "question": "What are your contributions on your thesis?", "answer": []}, {"key": 855, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "6 July 2021", "question": "Explain XSS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 856, "position": "Senior Application Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "6 July 2021", "question": "What is your ideal job like?", "answer": []}, {"key": 857, "position": "Senior Security Engineer, Applications Security", "company": "Genesys", "date": "5 July 2021", "question": "What is Threat Modeling? \r\nWhich Threat Modelling process you follow? Explain How do you perform threat modeling?\r\nWhat is Application Security Architecture Review? Explain  with an example?\r\nApplication Security Code Review Process? What is your approach in code review?\r\nWhat tools you use in Software composition analysis in your organization?\r\nExplain about Security pipelines used in current organization?\r\nWhich code review tools you use? How much level of manual code review you perform? How do you validate the security issues identified in Code Review Tools?\r\nExplain Application Penetration Testing Process?\r\nWhat is your favourite pentesting tool?\r\nHow you came into developement background?\r\nWhich is your favourite development language? What all tools developed by you?\r\nWhat type of common vulnerabilities you encounter when performing security code review?\r\nEncryption and hashing standards?\r\nWhat is cipher suite? How encryption take place in SSL/TLS handshake?\r\nWhat is your approach when performing security assessment on development frameworks?\r\nHave you worked on any SIEM solution? \r\nHave you worked on any Monitoring Solutions?", "answer": []}, {"key": 858, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "4 July 2021", "question": "Describe yourself professionally and why should we hire you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 859, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "BlueCross BlueShield of Tennessee", "date": "3 July 2021", "question": "I am not allowed to discuss the specific questions, but if you look at the job description it will set you up for success.", "answer": ["Just be yourself :-)"]}, {"key": 860, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange Business Services", "date": "2 July 2021", "question": "Basic network basics security basics fortigate", "answer": []}, {"key": 861, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "DISCO", "date": "2 July 2021", "question": "EDR\nNetwork Basics\nSecurity Basics \nScenarios", "answer": []}, {"key": 862, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Amadeus", "date": "1 July 2021", "question": "A question related to scenario, cyber security were covered", "answer": ["Almost all question correct"]}, {"key": 863, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange", "date": "1 July 2021", "question": "Technical related to telecom & endpoint Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 864, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Quotient", "date": "30 June 2021", "question": "Mostly the fundamentals of Networking", "answer": []}, {"key": 865, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forward Networks", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "Deep dive into Technical concepts and Behavioral questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 866, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forward Networks", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "Deep dive into Technical concepts and Behavioral questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 867, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Coinsquare", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "can you describe what CSRF is, and how you would mitigate it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 868, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Coinsquare", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "do you know what the OWASP top 10 are?", "answer": []}, {"key": 869, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "29 June 2021", "question": "They were pretty standard questions, tailored to the experience on my resume. There were a few things I stumbled on because I was nervous but they were patient and didn't expect me to be a walking encyclopedia. They were more interested in hearing my thought processes, seeing how I approached problems, and seeing how I handled stress.", "answer": []}, {"key": 870, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "\u0421\u0431\u0435\u0440\u041c\u0430\u0440\u043a\u0435\u0442", "date": "28 June 2021", "question": "Describe a OAuth autnorization flow", "answer": []}, {"key": 871, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Acuity Insurance", "date": "28 June 2021", "question": "A common one that seemed to come up a few times was regarding how you view security practices.", "answer": ["Answering it will various things like, least privilege, layered approach, etc opened a lot of discussion and gave me a chance to show how much I knew about broad best practices or my stance on things in the field. Less"]}, {"key": 872, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Iron Mountain", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Mostly asked about my experience based on my resume, and some use cases", "answer": []}, {"key": 873, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Nuveo", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Por qu\u00ea voc\u00ea est\u00e1 saindo da sua \u00faltima empresa?", "answer": []}, {"key": 874, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "CSRF, SOP, CORS, Path Traversal etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 875, "position": "Java Security Developer", "company": "Wipro", "date": "25 June 2021", "question": "Project Architecture with Rest services", "answer": []}, {"key": 876, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Everlaw", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "What would you do to prevent cross site scripting attacks?", "answer": []}, {"key": 877, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 878, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 June 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 879, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "23 June 2021", "question": "Have you ever dealt with an X scenario and how did you manage it? (SOC related questions)", "answer": []}, {"key": 880, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "23 June 2021", "question": "Do you know the MITRE framework?", "answer": []}, {"key": 881, "position": "Senior Network and Security Engineer", "company": "Cirrus Networks", "date": "22 June 2021", "question": "Routing Protocols - BGP\r\nSD-WAN Meraki\r\nSwitch port security", "answer": []}, {"key": 882, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "", "date": "22 June 2021", "question": "Can you say something about JSONP?", "answer": []}, {"key": 883, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "New York Times", "date": "21 June 2021", "question": "Standard culture fit and technical questions related to the role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 884, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "How would SOAP calls be tested in Burp?", "answer": []}, {"key": 885, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "What is Java Deserialization? How would you find it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 886, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "First Advantage", "date": "19 June 2021", "question": "What is an XXE injection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 887, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Resideo", "date": "18 June 2021", "question": "all around security and generic concepts of security", "answer": ["was able to answer from what i was already doing"]}, {"key": 888, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Seven Bridges", "date": "18 June 2021", "question": "Explain One of OWASP Top 10 vulnerabilities, detecion, explotation and fix.", "answer": []}, {"key": 889, "position": "Sr. Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "The Home Depot", "date": "17 June 2021", "question": "Tell me how you handled a situation where you need to explain a scenario to a non-technical person.\nTell me how you handled your task and was it finished within the deadline.", "answer": []}, {"key": 890, "position": "Security Quality Assurance Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "17 June 2021", "question": "Tell me about your internship experience?", "answer": []}, {"key": 891, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 June 2021", "question": "Describe your prior experience/walk me through your resume. \r\nComplete a coding exercise (live).", "answer": []}, {"key": 892, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Gusto", "date": "16 June 2021", "question": "Describe your prior experience/walk me through your resume. \r\nComplete a coding exercise (live).", "answer": []}, {"key": 893, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Phillips 66", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "1. Technical difference between Cisco, checkpoint and PaloAlto firewalls.\r\n2. How to configure next Gen firewalls in a network for the first time.", "answer": []}, {"key": 894, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Explain what deep packet analysis is/does.", "answer": []}, {"key": 895, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Explain the difference between segmentation and isolation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 896, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "How to troubleshoot a potential problem in a Linux environment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 897, "position": "Security Operations Engineer II", "company": "Qualtrics", "date": "15 June 2021", "question": "Difference between TCP and UDP.", "answer": []}, {"key": 898, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "14 June 2021", "question": "If you had a million dollar to fix a vulnerability class, which one would you choose and why?", "answer": ["Heap based buffer overflows. I\u2019d like to research mitigations that are backward-compatible with the C standard and that don\u2019t require changes to an existing code base. Similar to canaries on the stack. I\u2019d choose that, because this vuln class is frequently exploited and C is not going away any time soon although it\u2019s so old. Less"]}, {"key": 899, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Adjust", "date": "12 June 2021", "question": "What are the three qualities you want in a team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 900, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ECS Fin", "date": "12 June 2021", "question": "Questions ranging from web security, DLP, Vulnerability assessment, Network Security, Security engineering, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 901, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Workato", "date": "9 June 2021", "question": "Work experience related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 902, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Cruise", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "I was asked to walk through the thought process of working with a new API I've never seen before. I was presented an actual API, and was asked to free-form pseudocode a call to it.", "answer": ["While sharing my screen, I googled the service, scanned the docs, found relevant calls and began scaffolding pseudocode to auth with the API and pull the requested data. Less"]}, {"key": 903, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "LeQuest", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "tell us about your experience with security", "answer": []}, {"key": 904, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "Projects you did. \nTopics cover almost all areas.\ncryptography, secure coding, owasp top 10, network security (tcp, certificates etc), 1 thread modeling scenario.   \nBehavior question, like if developers refuse to fix the issue etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 905, "position": "Lead Info Security Engineer", "company": "HERE Technologies", "date": "8 June 2021", "question": "5 interviews with the same questions over and over, nonsense", "answer": []}, {"key": 906, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Benchling", "date": "7 June 2021", "question": "How to do a basic threat model", "answer": []}, {"key": 907, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ABB", "date": "4 June 2021", "question": "Overall security concepts were asked and good discussion", "answer": ["Good discussion"]}, {"key": 908, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "4 June 2021", "question": "What\u2019s your background and experience with SIEM and SOAR tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 909, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "31 May 2021", "question": "Why Gitlab and what value do you like about the company", "answer": []}, {"key": 910, "position": "Security Compliance Engineer", "company": "PierianDx", "date": "31 May 2021", "question": "How much experience do you have with GPDR?", "answer": []}, {"key": 911, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "The question were mainly on Cross site request forgery.", "answer": []}, {"key": 912, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "2. write a state-machine in verilog", "answer": []}, {"key": 913, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "3.  Synchronous and asynchronous cryptomodule\n4. what is CIA triade", "answer": []}, {"key": 914, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "1. what is secured boot-up?", "answer": []}, {"key": 915, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Eastern Bank", "date": "29 May 2021", "question": "Can you explain the TCP handshake?", "answer": ["Hello -  SYN, SYN-ACK, and ACK\r\nGood Bye -  FIN, FIN-ACK, and ACK\r\nRinse and Repeat - RST, RST-ACK and ACK Less"]}, {"key": 916, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Avant", "date": "29 May 2021", "question": "Asked what I knew about Windows endpoints and what I would do to protect them and verify they weren't vulnerable.", "answer": []}, {"key": 917, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Chronus", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "Difference between hashing encryption encoding.", "answer": []}, {"key": 918, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Chronus", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "Owasp top10", "answer": []}, {"key": 919, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Flo Health", "date": "28 May 2021", "question": "How would you keep vulnerability metrics up to date?", "answer": []}, {"key": 920, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Collabera", "date": "27 May 2021", "question": "How do you deal with conflict.", "answer": []}, {"key": 921, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "UST", "date": "27 May 2021", "question": "From basics", "answer": []}, {"key": 922, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Plume Design", "date": "26 May 2021", "question": "Questions around my previous work and setting up secure practices for networking team and so on", "answer": []}, {"key": 923, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synopsys", "date": "26 May 2021", "question": "CI / CD definitions, techniques applied during SAST", "answer": []}, {"key": 924, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Credible", "date": "25 May 2021", "question": "Behavioral questions, basic Security Interview questions, \"Do you know how to use kubernetes?\", \"Are you a cloud expert?\", \"How does x work?\", \"Explain y technology\", etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 925, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Credible", "date": "25 May 2021", "question": "Behavioral questions, basic Security Interview questions, \"Do you know how to use kubernetes?\", \"Are you a cloud expert?\", \"How does x work?\", \"Explain y technology\", etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 926, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "23 May 2021", "question": "How would you design a distributed web scraper?", "answer": []}, {"key": 927, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "How do you keep yourself up to date?", "answer": ["I am following some popular websites in cybersecurity, as well as the news."]}, {"key": 928, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "What are your 5 years plans?", "answer": ["I am aiming to get some certifications in my area such as CISSP, beside of this I am looking to get scripting skills such as Phython. Less"]}, {"key": 929, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "What is your most challenging day at work?", "answer": ["It was the day one of my team mate was absent, I handled most of her duties."]}, {"key": 930, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "Why you think this position is a good fit for you?", "answer": ["Based on the job description I found this position is good fit for my technical skills. Less"]}, {"key": 931, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Solvent CyberSecurity", "date": "22 May 2021", "question": "Why are you leaving your current position?", "answer": ["Ultimately, I\u2019ve learned a lot in my current role, but I\u2019m looking for the next step where I can continue to grow and use the skills I\u2019ve honed at a company I love, and this opportunity seems to be a great fit.\u201d Less"]}, {"key": 932, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "21 May 2021", "question": "Implement the queue class using only stacks.\nCreate a program that generates all valid strings from phone numbers and keypad.", "answer": []}, {"key": 933, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "21 May 2021", "question": "Generic, mostly non-technical questions. Lost my train of thought", "answer": []}, {"key": 934, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "20 May 2021", "question": "when you type in amazon.com on your browser, explain what happens?", "answer": ["Then USA amazon shopping portal website opens up."]}, {"key": 935, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "20 May 2021", "question": "What are some of the problems a workstation may not connect to a network?", "answer": ["Multiple of things can affect the workstation from not connecting. Such as if it was on the domain, is the IP address correct, is the NIC setup the right way, or if the firewall is blocking it from connecting. Less"]}, {"key": 936, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "18 May 2021", "question": "Q: Tell me about a time you made a mistake - how did you handle that?", "answer": []}, {"key": 937, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Faith Technologies Incorporated", "date": "17 May 2021", "question": "How do you set up the devscops model?\nWhat are your recommendations to mature the security posture of the organization?\nHow do you fit into the team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 938, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Blackboard", "date": "16 May 2021", "question": "Tell us more about your background.", "answer": []}, {"key": 939, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "13 May 2021", "question": "Cloud computing", "answer": []}, {"key": 940, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "PrimeRevenue", "date": "13 May 2021", "question": "Describe your coding ability in several languages", "answer": []}, {"key": 941, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "BenchSci", "date": "12 May 2021", "question": "What are the challenges I've seen in security and what did I want to accomplish in the senior security engineer role at Benchschi.", "answer": []}, {"key": 942, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange Business Services", "date": "12 May 2021", "question": "What is the routing looping ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 943, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "BMB", "date": "11 May 2021", "question": "Cisco, F5 , paloalto,forcepoint,ISE,FTD, FMC", "answer": []}, {"key": 944, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Oodle Car Finance", "date": "11 May 2021", "question": "Is there anything in the interview we could have done to attract you more to the company", "answer": []}, {"key": 945, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Clearco", "date": "10 May 2021", "question": "Describe your experience with SOAR platform, how did you set it up and what are the use-cases?", "answer": []}, {"key": 946, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "MindGeek", "date": "9 May 2021", "question": "Do you have experience with container security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 947, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "9 May 2021", "question": "I got many questions about firewalls, differences between multiple firewall types and IPS/IDS, and other networking-related questions. The Engineer holding my technical interview seemed rather a friendly senior colleague assessing my level of knowledge than someone judging me. There was no technical test for this role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 948, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "What are you looking for in this role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 949, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "Why do you want to leave your current role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 950, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "8 May 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in next 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 951, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "OWASP top 10, Remediation techniques and latest vulnerability trend", "answer": []}, {"key": 952, "position": "Info Security Engineer", "company": "Wells Fargo", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "Explain data level encryption.\nWhat is PKI and certificate management.", "answer": []}, {"key": 953, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Informatica", "date": "6 May 2021", "question": "Describe a situation from past work experience which was difficult .", "answer": []}, {"key": 954, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "6 May 2021", "question": "How would you describe a good manager you had worked with in the past?", "answer": []}, {"key": 955, "position": "Security Consulting Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "5 May 2021", "question": "Penetration Testing of web applications, APIs and thick client applications, threat modelling, cloud security, loggingand monitoring, Patching", "answer": []}, {"key": 956, "position": "Senior Security Site Reliability Engineer", "company": "Arkose Labs", "date": "4 May 2021", "question": "What's important to lead the team?", "answer": ["To be able to relate to the engineers at a level that makes feel safe and secure. Less"]}, {"key": 957, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synopsys", "date": "1 May 2021", "question": "questions were related to networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 958, "position": "AWS Security Engineer", "company": "LetsGetChecked", "date": "30 April 2021", "question": "How would you configure security tooling within an AWS account?", "answer": []}]